<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story title="1">
        <scene id="0" background="black" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The car has finally stopped.</text>
            <sound src="car door open.mp3"/>
            <text>A car door opens.</text>
            <text>Cold air rushes in, carrying with it the acrid stench of tobacco.</text>
            <speak chara="5">Achoo!</speak>
            <speak chara="0">…</speak>
            <speak chara="0">Get out of the car.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Oh.</speak>
            <text>I subconsciously reach for the right door, only to find it closed.</text>
            <speak chara="0">Tsk. Your left! Left!</speak>
            <text>The man grunts impatiently.</text>
            <text>Obediently, I feel my way towards the other side of the car, bent over like a shrimp.</text>
            <text>Fearing that my head would strike the door frame, I dare not straighten my back till I have taken two or three steps out of the car.</text>
            <text>Not that I have a choice. What kind of person puts a black bag over someone's head …?</text>
            <speak chara="0">Move.</speak>
            <text>The source of the voice grabs my arm, and without warning wrenches me forward. He is rather strong. Must be quite a burly chap.</text>
            <text>Thump.</text>
            <sound src="door close car away.mp3"/>
            <text>The sound of a car door slamming behind me, the sound of a starting engine.</text>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="5">Ah!</speak>
            <text>A momentary lapse of focus, and I slip, falling to the ground like an idiot.</text>
            <speak chara="0">Ya fool, watch where ya going!</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <text>If only I could actually see where I'm going.</text>
            <goto goto="5" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="5" background="forrestDark.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <sound src="walk on grass.mp3"/>
            <text>The ground feels sodden, and the air wafting from the cold earth saps what little heat remained inside the legs of my trousers.</text>
            <text>And so I walk, for how long I do not know.</text>
            <text>My surroundings grow quieter and quieter. I vaguely hear the mournful hooting of owls.</text>
            <text>It feels …</text>
            <text>… No, they're not planning to “dispose” of me, are they?</text>
            <text>After all, I'm an important “specimen”, so they wouldn't dare …</text>
            <text>Wait.</text>
            <sound src="write.mp3"/>
            <text>In front of me, it sounds like someone is writing or scribbling on something.</text>
            <speak chara="einNoFaceNoName">… You may go back now.</speak>
            <text>A female voice. Calm to the point of apathy. She doesn't sound very old. Perhaps a secretary of some sort.</text>
            <speak chara="0">Yes, Miss.</speak>
            <text>The big hand latched onto my arm finally releases its grip.</text>
            <text>I hear the flapping sound of a windbreaker, then the sound of footsteps slowly fading away.</text>
            <goto goto="10" />
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="schoolNight1.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="einNormalCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <sound src="cloth.mp3"/>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">Greenwich Mean Time, October 20, 22:57 — Thank you for bearing with us, little lab rat.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Ah!</speak>
            <text>Before I could even prepare myself, the hood on my head is suddenly whisked away with a 'swoosh'.</text>
            <text>The drawstring elastic near the mouth of the hood had scraped violently against my nose. Now it stings.</text>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">Quiet.</speak>
            <text>The messy-haired girl calmly commands me.</text>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">Follow me.</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalCloseNoName" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <text>She doesn't even give me the chance to get a proper look at her face.</text>
            <text>She too knows that I have nowhere else to run.</text>
            <goto goto="20" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="schoolNight1.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="horror.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <sound src="walk slow.mp3"/>
            <text>A university campus. Harsh light from street lamps scatter off the bitumen, casting eerie shadows. I see pale lighting from a building up ahead, and it reminds of those terrible experiments.</text>
            <text>As I walk, unable to stop, I begin to imagine myself as that desperate, pathetic figure fleeing for my life.</text>
            <text>Fingers chewed raw.</text>
            <text>Clothes torn to shreds.</text>
            <text>Hysterically screaming.</text>
            <text>Deliriously waving my hands about —</text>
            <text>To be eventually shot down with a tranquiliser gun.</text>
            <text>Or worse.</text>
            <text remark="next">“Where you shall hear the howls of desperation,”</text>
            <text remark="next">“and see the ancient spirits in their pain,”</text>
            <text remark="next">“as each of them laments his second death — ”</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19kizjVUiE6CvKADa98">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note:</p>
                <p class="article-text">The quotation recalled by our protagonist is from Dante's “Divine Comedy” (Mandelbaum translation, Inferno Canto I.) </p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="30" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="schoolNight3.jpg" bgm="no">
            <show chara="einNormalCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einSmileCloseNoName">Don't be afraid. This place is different from the other laboratories.</speak>
            <text>!</text>
            <text>… She sees through me, straight to the anxiety within my heart.</text>
            <show chara="einSmileCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSmileCloseNoName">Imperial Institute, Lab 42.</speak>
            <text>She speaks, as if to herself —</text>
            <show chara="einSmileCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSmileCloseNoName">Welcome home.</speak>
            <text>Home?</text>
            <goto goto="40"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="studyNight.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="einNormalCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">Sit.</speak>
            <text>The girl points to the sofa in the entrance hall.</text>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">Tea? Or coffee?</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">I recommend tea. The air in London is terrible.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalCloseNoName">…</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSeriousAhCloseNoName">Ein-Stein.</speak>
            <text>She suddenly and solemnly speaks in German. Ein … Stein … “One Stone”?</text>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Doctor, Einstein — Lieserl Albert Einstein.</speak>
            <text>She points to herself, and then to me.</text>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Your name?</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Omega 1. It's in my files. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Ω1 is not a human name.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Then I don't have one.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">How inconvenient.</speak>
            <text>She shakes her head.</text>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <text>Even so, I can't do anything about that. After all —</text>
            <show chara="einSmileClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSmileClose">… Welt. W.E.L.T. </speak>
            <speak chara="5">Eh?</speak>
            <speak chara="einSmileClose">I feel this name is just right for you. </speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Any name would do.</speak>
            <text>“Ω” = “W”. “Welt” = “World”. Indeed, as an outcast of the world, to have such a name would be most amusing. </text>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Now then, let's go through your physical checkup, Welt.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Okay. </speak>
            <text>Once again, I'll need to put on a lot of electrodes — perhaps a blood draw, or even a bone marrow biopsy. Well, I'm used to it all by now.</text>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSeriousAhClose">No, no need to get up. Just stay put.</speak>
            <speak chara="einSeriousAhClose">Show me your soul.</speak> <!-- Lost in translation. The translator has chosen to use a different pun instead. The original light novel online (not VN) explictly mentions "Show me your genitals".-->
            <speak chara="5">Oh …</speak>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="5">… Eh? S-Soul??</speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhCloseNoName" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSeriousAhClose">Take off your shoes and socks. I need to thoroughly examine your sole.</speak>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="5">— What for?!</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">It's getting very late, we should finish up and rest soon.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Huh?!</speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">One can precisely and intuitively determine the state of someone's health by looking at their sole. Also, the inspection process is rather quick —</speak>
            <show chara="einSmileClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSmileClose">— Just grab a toothbrush and brush you up a bit, that should do it.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Wait …</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… You mean, we can just calmly waltz off to bed after that?!</speak>
            <speak chara="einSmileClose">Correct. Your comprehension skills are remarkable.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… That doesn't make any sense!</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Indeed.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Huh?</speak>
            <show chara="einSmileClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einSmileClose">Seeing Welt so depressed, Dr Einstein decided she'd tell a joke to lift his spirits.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <text>What the hell is wrong with this “doctor”?</text>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">You'll sleep in Room 105 over there.</speak>
            <text>The girl points down a corridor to the side. </text>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">I live upstairs.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">… Oh.</speak>
            <speak chara="einNormalClose">Good night. You can forget your past identity as a little lab rat.</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>She walks away, without a single backward glance.</text>
            <text>Leaving behind a “little lab rat”, rooted to the floor, dumbfounded.</text>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <goto goto="50"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="hospital.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">…</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">The man now named “Welt” couldn't understand what just happened. Ever since the day he started forming memories again, nobody else had so casually given him such a baffling degree of freedom — even though “the day he started remembering” was not that long ago.</p>
                <p class="article-text">It was this same season, three years ago, when he first opened his eyes to a scene of chaos. Unfamiliar men and women were inspecting him, asking him all sorts of questions, questions that one would only ask a lost child..</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“What is your name?”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">“Where do you live?”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">“What is your nationality?”</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“…”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">It was a strange feeling — you undoubtedly knew all the answers, yet you could not “congeal” or solidify those answers in your brain. It was as if all the neurons that wove the sea of your memories were fried.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“I don't know”</p>
                <p class="article-text">This was the one response that the young man could muster.</p>
                <p class="article-text">He could still remember how to speak — yet he didn't know whether this was something he should be grateful for.  German, English, Russian, Latin …  even Japanese and Chinese. He couldn't remember how he came to understand so many languages.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“Who am I?”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">He quite naturally retorted with such a question.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“We don't know either”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">The others replied. Then they unleashed a torrent of conversation, though they might as well have been speaking to themselves.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“Schicksal”. Our “Destiny”. A secret organisation with a long history. The true masters of the world, the saviours of humanity.</p>
                <p class="article-text">“Honkai”. The “Collapse”. The one calamity that science has yet to explain completely. Since the dawn of civilisation, it has polluted the human world, transforming peaceful creatures into terrifying demons. These monsters or “Honkai Beasts”, in their alien plastic flesh, strike fear into us all.</p>
                <p class="article-text">“Myself”. I, who lost my memory, was the sole survivor of a Honkai event. Its location was Berlin, where it had originated from some  multi-storeyed building.</p>
                <p class="article-text">“My body”. Within this fortunate body of mine hides a great secret — for the sake of saving more people, I must accept their plans for experimentation on my body: it is my only option.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">One month. Another month. Month after month.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">One year. Another year. Year after year.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">The young man, code-named “Ω1”, was taken from one laboratory to another, to repeat the exact same thing, over and over again.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">To bear the unbearable, suffer the insufferable.</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">“Please cooperate with us.”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">“Please consider it for the sake of humanity.”</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">“These are unavoidable side effects.”</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">A flock of lunatic scientists. Saving humanity and what not: it's all just a load of hogwash.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Did you not say that I am a fortunate survivor? Then why do I have to needlessly suffer through such manner of misfortune?</p>
                <p class="article-text">The “humanity” that you repeatedly emphasise, who are they really? Where is your humanity?</p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">There were moments where I really wanted to just die and be done with it.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">…</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">If it wasn't for that chatterbox who kept checking in on me.</p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="60" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="letter.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text-h">To Ω:</p>
                <p class="article-text">A good October to you. Time flies: this would already be my 22nd letter to you — last time I had finished telling you the story of the Lady Saint. But before I seek new stories to regale, let us first discuss what is happening around us.</p>
                <p class="article-text">I have already heard of the terrible incident in September, and I apologise on their behalf. Well, it just so happens that there is a new laboratory: I anticipate you will be able to transfer to it soon. Whether the circumstances will be more favourable than your previous lab, that I cannot say for certain — because from what I hear, the new person in charge is a lady with a rather “earnest” personality.</p>
                <p class="article-text">However, I must inform you from the standpoint of Schicksal: all the experiments you've been through, have been for the continued survival of a certain species on this planet, one so-called “Homo sapiens” — hence your continued and necessary suffering. The world will always treat some people unfairly, and this is something none of us can really change.</p>
                <p class="article-text">It has already been three years since the disaster in Berlin. The city has already begun its reconstruction. The people will slowly forget the horrors of that night.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Yet we all know that, at this present moment, a sinister power continues to grow and fester within the rift of space-time. It spared you back then, but it did not spare the others. If we are able to truly fathom the logic behind this phenomenon, then we “Homo sapiens” will be able to live up to our name, to use our sapience to conquer the natural world — then no one will ever need to spend another day living in fear or delusion, deceiving themselves and others.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Yes, this is most unfair to you; in fact the most recent events have been particularly unjust to you. But if only for my sake, I hope you can understand and forgive everything. The fate of all humanity, in a certain sense, rests upon your shoulders.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text-h">P.S.</p>
                <p class="article-text"> Concerning your background before your memory loss: as far as I know, the relevant department should still be looking into this — but as you may already recognise, it has been more than three years since the incident, and the possibility of getting any results will only become slimmer with time. But I don't believe that so-called “Child of Honkai” Theory. You can't be a Herrscher, right?</p>
                <p class="article-text">Perhaps the arrival of new technology will bring about some unexpected turnaround of the whole situation … who knows? The new laboratory really isn't that bad; in fact, I believe when you get there you'll be quite willing to cooperate with them — trust me.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text-s">Your old pal，</p>
                <p class="article-text-s">Clown Alpha</p>
                <p class="article-text-s">1955.10.2.</p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="70"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="weltRoomNight1.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="5">Huh … That guy, he sounded so casual …</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Yet … I'm sure everyone has their own problems to deal with.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">After all, he was just some anonymous pen pal arranged for me by some anonymous bigwig.</speak>
            <speak chara="5">But his story about a certain “Saint Kallen” did touch me. I definitely had not planned on paying so much attention to that type of propaganda or political drivel —</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Since when did I start looking forward to his monthly story updates?</speak>
            <speak chara="5">Sigh …</speak>
            <text>“105”. A musty-smelling wooden door is carelessly left ajar.</text>
            <text>This must be the room where the strange girl has allowed me to spend the night. The lifeless linen curtains, the walls that seem more at home at a mortuary. Indeed, this is a décor most befitting of a laboratory —</text>
            <goto goto="72" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="72" background="weltRoomNight3.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>Mm? There's bread and snacks on this desk. Are they for me to eat?</text>
            <text>…</text>
            <text>Munch munch.</text>
            <speak chara="5">…</speak>
            <speak chara="5">My God! What's in this slice of bread?!</speak>
            <speak chara="5">How can it be so delicious?!</speak>
            <speak chara="5">This indescribable aroma of mushrooms! </speak>
            <speak chara="5">And this bacon that tastes just perfect! </speak>
            <speak chara="5">There are simply no words to describe this rich and mellow aftertaste!</speak>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="5">How can it be so delicious!</speak>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="5">It's great to be alive indeed!</speak>
            <goto goto="75" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="75" background="black" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>Munch munch.</text>
            <text>Munch munch munch munch.</text>
            <text>Munch munch munch munch munch munch.</text>
            <text>… … … …</text>
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <sound src="mid-lude.mp3"/>
            <text>And thus, fully satisfied, having indulged in a delicacy of unsurpassed quality, Welt sinks into a deep slumber.</text>
            <text>The next day —</text>
            <goto goto="80"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="weltRoomDay1.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="morning.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>There was a heavy rainstorm in the middle of the night —  opening the windows, one can sense the air is especially fresh and clean, leading one to doubt that this place could have ever been the birthplace of the Industrial Revolution.</text>
            <text>Not far from here, perched on tree branches are several sparrows chirping constantly, having a lively discussion about the sun as it rises above the horizon.</text> <!-- 山雀 = Titmouse but sparrow chosen here to avoid ambiguity re: tit-->
            <text>At the first glimmer of dawn, a butterfly emerges from some dark crevice, languidly crawling across the window frame.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFaceNoName">Hey.</speak>
            <text>The butterfly beats its wings twice, then disappears into the azure sky.</text>
            <text>As the sunshine pierces the tree leaves and thickets, to spill upon his body, the young man can feel the hard lump within his heart begin to thaw and dissolve.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFaceNoName">Hey!</speak>
            <text>What an incredible evening. What an incredible morning.</text>
            <text>How long has it been since I experienced such peaceful tranquillity?</text>
            <text>Whether it be wind or rain, or the song of birds, or the buzzing drone of flying insects —</text>
            <text>At this very moment, even if there were some loud commotion，it won't matter too much …</text>
            <goto goto="84" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="84" background="black" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="morning.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <sound src="hit man.mp3"/>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFaceNoName">Oi!! I'm speaking to you!!!</speak>
            <text>The young man felt a heavy blow strike the back of his head..</text>
            <text>And now it's oh so dark …</text>
            <text>Eh? Why have the sparrows flown to the top of my head, and why are they now doing circles around it?</text>
            <goto goto="85" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="85" background="weltRoomDay2.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <shake position="all" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">Really, are you deaf? I've called you several times already! You're lucky that I had the good will to pry the door open and charge in.</speak>
            <text>The assailant, a red-haired girl with twin pony tails, fiercely scolds the young man — who had fallen, and is now seated on the ground, staring at the birds above his head. She also happens to be wearing a white labcoat.</text>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltSurpriseClose">… You are?</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">Huh? No one introduced m—</speak>
            <text>As she reaches mid-sentence, the eyes of the twin-tailed girl wander and fall upon the empty plate.</text>
            <text> Quietly it sits on the only desk in the room.</text>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <text>Twintails closes her eyes. With utmost concentration she brings her nose towards it, and sniffs.</text>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">Oi! You … y-y-you didn't eat something made of truffles, did you?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltSurpriseClose">Truffle?</speak>
            <speak chara="weltSurpriseClose">Uh … the plate was originally filled with bread slices …  mixed with some kind of mushroom … Is this “truffle” you speak of some kind of mushroom?</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">…</speak>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <text>The twin-tailed redhead rolls her eyes and almost faints.</text>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName"> Some kind of mushroom? You're telling me that truffles are merely “some kind of mushroom”? Damn it, doesn't that mophead idiot think so too?!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">… Hmm?</speak>
            <text>She has just discovered that, beside the empty plate, there are also several other knicknacks of a “suspicious nature”, sitting on the desk.</text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">Tsk tsk tsk tsk … Comfit … Atomic fireball … Dark chocolate …</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName"> How can one mix truffles together with such cheap, inferior snacks?!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <text>As she examines the sweets, she begins unwrapping  and tossing them into her mouth — that is, until she notices something in the corner of the room.</text>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">Oh? What's this? A welcome card?</speak>
            <text>It turns out that greeting cards are indeed inedible.</text>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">Urghhhhh!</speak>
            <text>The young man by the window suddenly screams in delirium.</text>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">… Hmm? What trick are you pulling this time?</speak>
            <text>The young man shouts incoherently, as if he has given up all sense of dignity.</text>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <text>Before long, he is clasping his head in surrender, pulling himself into the shape of a ball.</text>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">Hehe …</speak>
            <text>The young woman seems to have understood something.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">May ~ I ~ open ~ and ~ take ~a ~ look?</speak>
            <text>The red-haired assailant changed her tone, speaking as if she were an actor in a radio drama. </text>
            <text>Caught in a trance, the young man sees the illusion of a candle and a whip appear before him.</text>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“To the most respectable Mr Ω1: greetings.”</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“Because I do not know your name, I will address you as such for now, and for this I am truly sorry.”</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">Erhm, why have you never been this polite with me?</speak>
            <text>The manner of her comment is reminiscent of a jealous father-in-law.</text>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“From today onwards, you are a member of the Imperial Institute, Lab 42. Of course, our laboratory has nothing to do with the British Government, but is instead an independent organisation under the direct authority of Schicksal Headquarters.”</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“Unlike other laboratories equipped with heavy physico-chemical facilities, we are a research institution based on Galois Theory Analysis and Turing Machine Simulation, so it will not have much of a visible impact on your life or wellbeing.”</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">Hmph … Ω1, what she has written here, do you understand?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“What you may not know is that I have been paying close attention to you since the disaster three years ago.”</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaSnickerCloseNoName">“You as a specimen. You as a life. You as a human being. In a sense, your existence has already left an indelible mark on my life.”</speak>
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">— URGHHHHH!</speak>
            <text>The red-haired assailant suddenly loses all composure, wildly waving a clenched fist in the air.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">… Damn it! Despicable! Bloody despicable!… This is most certainly intentional harassment! … I bet she absolutely intended for me to read this!</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">You!</speak>
            <text>She points with two fingers, and glares contemptuously at the young man huddled on the floor.</text>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">Yes???</speak>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">Are you also familiar with this kind of saucy word play — h-h-here!?  Here, besides a “research lifestyle”, there can be no other hidden motives, okay? … Hmm?!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">Of … Of course! N-no matter what it sounds like, yesterday was my first time meeting her!</speak>
            <text>The poor young man, now with his face completely flushed, seems even less persuasive.</text>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">…</speak>
            <text>The glare of the twin-tailed girl is so terrifying, it is as though her eyes could fire death lasers at any moment.</text>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">… The way you read it out, I too felt very humiliated!</speak>
            <text>The young man dares not make eye contact with her, hugging his head as he pours more fuel on the fire with his poor choice of words.</text>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryCloseNoName">…</speak>
            <text>The girl takes a moment to glare at the young man, with a look of one gazing upon garbage, before closing her eyes.</text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName">Forget it, I'll let this slide for now. But if I ever find you harbouring any impure intentions, this lady here will be the first to castrate you!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">Eek!</speak>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">（continued）</p>
                <p class="article-text">… I know the people you have just met may not be particularly convincing. But please believe in this — it is here that you will build a brand new life for yourself.</p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text-s">In Gourmet Dining We Trust, </p>
                <p class="article-text-s">Dr Lieserl Albert Einstein</p>
                <p class="article-text-s">1955.10.20</p>
            </text>
            <text>After grudgingly reading through the final details of the card, the disgruntled twin-tailed girl finally remembers something —</text>
            <show chara="teslaBoringCloseNoName" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaBoringCloseNoName">By the way, you don't recognise who I am, do you?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringCloseNoName" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <text>With hesitation and fear, the young man nodded.</text>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaBoringClose">Let me introduce myself … Nikola Tesla. You can just call me Tesla.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraClose">Simply put, all you need to know is that I am also one of the directors of this lab.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaEmbarraClose">Those “mushrooms” you ate, they were my private property, and they were very dear to me. Do you understand?</speak>
            <text>She angrily seizes the young man's shirt.</text>
            <show chara="teslaBoringClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaBoringClose">Let's go,  there are already people in the living room.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltSurpriseClose">… People?</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaAngryClose">I mean that gourmet food thief! Who else?!</speak>
            <goto goto="90"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG1.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Good morning, Dr Tesla — how was today's breakfast?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Good morning, Eins — Hmph.</speak>
            <text>Tugging at Welt's collar, Twintails pouts and tuts disapprovingly.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… You vile bitch, how can you pretend everything is fine?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It seems the sausage quiche suits your appetite. That is most wonderful indeed.</speak>
            <text>Despite being rudely berated, the girl with the mop-shaped hair continues to recline peacefully on the sofa, and with an air of indifference bites into a pastry sandwich.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> Well, after all, it's filled with grease and packed with energy — hey, no, don't you change the subject!</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> Pfff. You are rather lively today, Dr Tesla.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… If it wasn't for you, you treacherous thief! Hmph!</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Thief?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr Einstein doesn't quite understand what Dr Tesla is talking about.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Don't you play dumb! That bag of truffles, it was you who took it from my room without my permission, wasn't it?</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">…</speak>
            <text>Mophead immediately begins wagging her index finger back and forth, as though she had already anticipated her response. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr Einstein would like to give a friendly reminder —</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace" remark="next">— Even if Dr Tesla enjoys travelling to Trieste for vacation, it does not mean that the bag of mushrooms is Dr Tesla's personal property.</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19jgf4aT8mx5i123cv3">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note:</p>
                <p class="article-text">Trieste is a port city on the border between Italy and Slovenia. It was once prosperous as a major port of the Austro-Hungarian Empire. The Friuli region, to which it belongs, is one of the major producers of truffles. The city is also home to the International Centre for Theoretical Physics.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Tesla is Croatian-American, and Trieste has a similar climate to her homeland.</p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Y-y-y-y-you say what? I got those truffles after much blood, sweat and tears. Are you mistaken?!</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Also, truffles are not mushrooms! You calling them that is a slight on their honour!</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Hah …</speak>
            <text>Begrudgingly, Mophead lets out a long sigh.</text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The truffles were purchased with laboratory funds. Naturally, they become public property. Any other questions?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… I-it's called a loan! I'll pay back next time when I have the money! Make no mistake!</speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">If Dr Tesla continues to persist with her false claims, Dr Einstein will have no choice but to report this embezzlement of public funds to Headquarters.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">…</speak>
            <text>The corner of Tesla's mouth twitches a few times, before she finally chooses to change the subject.</text>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="studyDay.jpg" bgm="no">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraClose" position="center"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This guy locked himself in the bedroom and just sat there, in a daze. Made me think he was going to commit suicide.</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Uh … Who's thinking of committing suicide?!</speak>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Who? Do you know how many times I knocked on that door? Huh?? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Not to mention you have a history of depression?!</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Sorry … for a moment I was just daydreaming …</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Forgive him, Dr Tesla. You're being too anxious.</speak>
            <text>Einstein licks the salt granules from her fingertips.</text>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Tsk. You two have a call-and-response thing going … Don't tell me you're long-lost lovers?</speak>
            <text>Twintail's brow furrows into the shape of a mountain.</text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr Einstein would never find such a pathetic boyfriend.</speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltShameClose">Uh, uh that is — incorrect! How am I pathetic?!</speak>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">You surrendered yourself to despair.</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The unemployed are inclined to abandon themselves to despair.</speak>
            <text>With a “puff”, Mophead stands up from her sofa “nest”.</text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">So we have decided to give you a job.</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">… Job?</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Lab assistant.</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">… Assistant? I —</speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> Basically, you're no longer a little lab rat. You are now our companion. Let us rejoice.</speak>
            <text>Twintails speaks with the solemn monotone of one reciting scripture.</text>
            <show chara="teslaNormalClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr Tesla, we need to tell him exactly what he is doing, his specific responsibilities.</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmm … to put it simply: to serve us and keep us happy?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…?</speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">
			For example, serve us tea and water, cook our meals, do our laundry, and if there is nothing left to do, scrub the floors and brush the toilets …</speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmClose" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Ahem.</speak>
            <text>Mophead clears her throat in a deliberate manner.</text>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I'm just joking! With a dull, simple, pretty toy-boy like you, even if you had wanted to be our servant, we would never accept …</speak> <!-- 小白脸 = "little white face", a derogatory term for a gigolo.-->
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhClose" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Ahem.</speak>
            <text>Mophead clears her throat, this time more loudly.</text>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> Okay okay I'll explain it properly! Obviously, I'm normally not this long-winded…</speak>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <hide position="right"/>
            <text>Out of nowhere, Twintails whisks out a pair of red-framed glasses, and reluctantly puts them on.</text>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Uh-huh … Listen well, toy-boy. Generally speaking, the role of a lab assistant is to assist in experiments, obviously. Unfortunately, you are clearly lacking in this capability, aren't you?</speak>
            <text>The young man nods.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">However, we believe you can improve our work efficiency. Not only that, but you will also do yourself some good.</speak>
            <text>The young man tilts his head, looking somewhat lost and vacant.</text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Your job is to plan our days off work. Arrange our leisure and entertainment. Saves us from working so hard for our vacation, only to have to waste more brainpower deciding our own entertainment.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Of course, you may also participate in said activities. Doesn't sound too bad, does it?</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Is there anything I haven't explained clearly? Again, to put it in simple terms, your job is to take us out to have fun.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">But don't disturb us during work hours. Go idle by yourself in the library, or just go for a casual stroll around the place —</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">— But don't go strolling so far as to make this organisation think you're going to escape. We don't want to have to deal with the plainclothed coppers.</speak> <!-- 便衣 = "Plain-clothed" (policemen) -->
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Oi! Is it okay or not? If you don't agree, we can always send you back, all right?!</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">…</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey! You stupid?</speak>
            <text>Begrudgingly, the girl with the red-rimmed spectacles waves her hands in front of the young man's eyes.</text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Dr Einstein believes that Welt is simply going through a state of shock and astonishment at the news.</speak>
            <show chara="einSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">… Lieserl! Are you some troll from “The Lord of the Rings”? Stop using “Doctor this” or “Doctor that” to address us. It's getting very annoying!</speak> <!-- The VN uses 兽人 = "orc", not "troll" -->
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX192eVQJxmFnhxbdYPSj">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note:</p>
                <p class="article-text"> JRR Tolkien's “The Lord of the Rings” was first published in the United Kingdom on July 29, 1954, in the form of its first volume “The Fellowship of the Ring”.</p>
                <p class="article-text">Tolkien had planned to compile “The Lord of the Rings” into a single volume for publication, but the idea could not be realised because of postwar shortages in material and paper.</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… Wait.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… Who's “Welt”?</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… Is it this little toy-boy?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">… Lieserl! Don't tell me that's the name you gave him?</speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Wait, were you referring to me as “little toy-boy”?!</speak>
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX18SorRINadIetIkimT9"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
