<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <img>
        <image src="re_doHisDuty.jpg" type="background"/>
    </img>
    <story title="1">
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="newChapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="londonStreet.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_p.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You two, what are you on about, whispering like that?!</speak>
            <text>Twintails complains, while tossing everything she is carrying straight into Welt's arms. </text>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Da-da-danger! </speak>
            <text>With great difficulty, the young man manages to grab one bag after another, as they fly towards him in quick succession. In a state of panic, he spits out — </text>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">We're in the middle of a street! What should we do if something breaks? </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You pay. </speak>
            <text>Tesla shrugs, matter-of-factly. </text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … You're being too much of a bully. </speak>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmph, since the Finn was left over on the other side to handle the translation and archaeological work, you shall now automatically assume his “male duties”. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Is that too hard to understand? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Oh, and if Planck had not run off to Vienna, she could've also shared these menial tasks with you … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">（ … It's indeed hard to understand. Perhaps it'd be better to ask why a person like you had to go everywhere and buy bags upon bags of useless stuff. ）</speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">（ … And wasn't it you who clearly said, “No problem, no problem, you two can go ahead and leave us”? ）</speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">To translate for you —  She's actually asking you what “we” were just talking about. </speak>
            <text>Einstein, who is leading the way by herself, stretches lazily and explains without looking back at Welt. </text>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … What? </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> …  I-is that really her intent? </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey,  I'm not that awkward, alright?! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">So you should respond to her: Eins is introducing you to the history of Northern Ireland and the city of Londonderry, something that Eins is very familiar with — </speak>
            <text>Refusing to acknowledge Twintails' complaints in the slightest, Mophead speaks according to standard protocol, as though she were minding her own business — </text>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> — and in so doing, to show you how Celtic culture is gradually being eroded by Anglo-Saxon culture. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Hmm … just now I should be detailing the differences between Scotland, Wales and Ireland … </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">What the … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaSmileGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <text> After hearing the actual details of the “conspiratorial whispering” between Einstein and Welt, Tesla's expression instantly brightened. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Last time you said you've been to Ireland, was it actually here? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaSmileGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Mm-hmm. At that time, it was not easy to buy air tickets, so I left from here for New York by ship. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Ship? </speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Mm. it was the first time I left home for long-distance travel … I was quite happy, actually. Although the time spent on the journey was rather long. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah … was that twenty years ago? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Huh? </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Tesla, it was nine years ago. Your answer was off by more than ten … </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Twenty years ago … how old were you yourself … </speak>
            <goto goto="15" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="15" background="londonStreet2.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_b.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="planckSisterBlackClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="planckSisterNoFace">According to the itinerary, today we will rest here for a day — then we will cross the Atlantic. </speak>
            <speak chara="planckSisterNoFace">We have a rare day to spend on land — is there anything you want to play? </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … Teacher, why, you are acting like a child in school. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> Instead of wasting time “playing”, I feel it's better if we just find a comfortable place to do some light reading … </speak>
            <speak chara="planckSisterNoFace"> … Fräulein Einstein, are you trying to make me happy or sad? </speak>
            <speak chara="planckSisterNoFace"> … No, today you must accompany me and we shall do this and that together! </speak>
            <speak chara="planckSisterNoFace"> … Let's go, we shall climb the city walls! </speak>
            <goto goto="17" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="17" background="londonStreet.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_p.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You … You still remember such things so clearly. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I say … when I was seven or eight, those places my grandpa took me to  — I've long since forgotten what they're like. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Anyway, it was in the Croatian countryside. Some backwater where birds won't even bother crapping in. Wasn't particularly interesting anyway. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No, I also don't have much of an impression of what happened when I was young. It's just a coincidence that I retain this fragment of memory. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Huh? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">But if one was interested enough in a place, they would naturally seek a lot of information about it. Slowly, one would become as familiar with the local customs as they are with the back of their hand. </speak> <!-- 如数家珍 = "to be familiar with a subject matter as though one is enumerating their family valuables" -->
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … It's indeed horrifying, a theorist's obsessive pursuit of knowledge. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">At any rate, it's better than those experimentalists who blow the roof off at the drop of a hat. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Oh, then that's better yet again than those experimenters who destroy the world at the flick of a switch. </speak>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … HEY THAT'S EVEN MORE OUTRAGEOUS! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">So, on the fifth weekend of October, 1955 AD, three young souls  —  two women and one man, in a burst of laughter and jeering —  ascended the walls of Londonderry, the best-preserved urban defensive structure in all of Europe since the Age of Enlightenment. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text"> At that moment, they would have never thought that, in this Irish city, they would experience one of the most important events of their lives.</p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="derryWall.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_p.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Londonderry was originally only called Derry. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Of course, it has nothing to do with the “Delhi” in India. Instead it comes from the Irish “Daire” — meaning “oak forest”. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Later, a London chamber of commerce came here to colonise and develop the land, so they assigned the prefix “London” to the city's name. </speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">People from the colonial period seemed to enjoy naming things like this … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Whether it's New York or Rhode Island, there are no few examples of people directly copying a European place name. </speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19HAOD7GN9woHXyw4Jp">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">Rhode Island is one of the thirteen states that originally formed the United States. Its full name is “the State of Rhode Island and Providence Plantations”, of which the name “Rhode Island” is derived from the Greek island of Rhodes (Ρόδος). </p>
                <p class="article-text">Providence, the state capital, is home to Brown University, and is also the hometown of Howard Phillips Lovecraft (1890-1937), a famous novelist and creator of the Cthulhu mythology. </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Because it was a city developed by Londoners — </speak>
            <text>Einstein continued her explanation unceasingly, completely ignoring the side-commentary from Tesla, </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> — whether it was in the choice of location, or the planning of its central urban district, in both respects the city deliberately imitated London. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace" remark="next"> From the current point of view, the main difference is probably …  that the water quality of the River Foyle is much better than the River Thames. </speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19HAOD7GN9woHXyw4Jp">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">The River Foyle is the main river that nurtures Londonderry, with its clear waters and rich biodiversity. </p>
                <p class="article-text">Londonderry's position relative to the river and its estuary was intentional — the city planners deliberately imitated London's position relative to the Thames. </p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Like the London City Wall, the Derry City Wall was also arranged in an approximate square or diamond shape; this was relatively rare for European cities. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Of course, compared to London, the names of the city gates here are much more arbitrary, such as the “Shipquay Gate” right in front of us — so named because the gate faces the quay for overseas shipping. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Similarly, going clockwise from the East, we see such gates as the “Ferryquay Gate”, “Bishop's Gate”, and “Butcher's Gate”. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Derry is one of the few “virgin cities” in European history whose walls have never been breached since her founding — in 1689, she experienced a 105-day siege but was able to hold firm. </speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Be that as it may … Ultimately, didn't it also have something to do with the remoteness of this place? </speak>
            <text>Twin-tails retorts somewhat incredulously. </text>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No, no, no.  </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">At the time, it was an important hub connecting the British mainland with her American colonies, and many Irish immigrants set off from here for the New World. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShyWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Indeed, there is so much history … </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">It feels like you've always been interested in Ireland, am I right? </speak>
            <show chara="weltShyWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Actually it all started here … from this very city … </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> When you realise the beauty of a culture, you will voluntarily search and dig up more information. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Ireland is such a place to me. Shouldn't it be similar to someone else's interest in India? </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Indeed I have read many books on Indian philosophy. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">However, unlike your situation, it is completely impossible for me to wholeheartedly embrace Indian culture. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … ? </speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Is it really that hard to understand? A caste system that divides people into four classes, from high to low — such a system should be extinguished. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">That … that wasn't what I meant just now … </speak>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Eh … indeed, Tesla, you don't need to be so sensitive around such topics. </speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Having said that, about that clue we specifically came for — do we really have a clear objective? </speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Of course we do. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_p.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Wait a moment … </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Right here! </speak>
            <goto goto="25" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="25" background="CG7-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeEin.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>What was originally a mere “jaunt” around the one mile that is the Derry City Wall — </text>
            <text> — has now evolved into something more, as Mophead suddenly lies down in front of a cannon on the wall, taking out a flashlight from her pocket and holding it in her mouth. </text>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Wh-why so sudden … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ye-yes indeed, what's going on here? </speak>
            <text>Welt and Tesla both seem puzzled. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">There are still 24 such cannons left. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Oh … so what's so special about this one? </speak>
            <text>Twintails shrugs, conveying her confusion. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">This one is also nothing special. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Huh? </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It's just that the pointer jumped. </speak>
            <text>Einstein pulls out some army-green device from her front pocket. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">What's this … a Geiger counter? </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">The Geiger counter, also known as the Geiger-Müller counter, is a particle detector used to detect ionising radiation. It is usually used to detect alpha rays (proton-and-neutron particles) and beta rays (electron particles), while some models can detect gamma rays (ultra-high frequency electromagnetic waves) and x-rays. </p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Is there a radioactive source here?! </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No … </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">This is the trace Honkai energy detector that I let Ada convert from a Geiger counter some time ago. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> Doesn't it look fashionable? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … Fashionable?! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I say it looks pretty intimidating … </speak>
            <text>Twintails sneers and turns up her nose at Mophead's fashion sense. </text>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Wait … </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Who's Ada? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">An assistant, just an assistant. Not much different from that Finn. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Rather than gossip about that, let's first find this information left behind by that other party. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Well. </speak>
            <text>Mophead places her hands together in a style mimicking Sherlock Holmes. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The story may have just begun. </speak>
            <goto goto="33" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="33" background="CG7-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeEin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Here. </speak>
            <text>After some length of time, Mophead, who had already been lying flat on the ground, points her finger towards a position on the underside of the cannon, and both companions also notice an abnormally-painted layer of black pitch. </text>
            <text> Einstein glances around, and seeing that no one else is nearby, takes out a knife and scrapes the body of the cannon a few times — </text>
            <text>And a line of silver inscription is clearly revealed. </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:#EDEDED;font-style:italic;">The innocent queen has both her eyes blindfolded. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text" style="color:#EDEDED;font-style:italic;">H.A. </p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="34" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="34" background="derryWall.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_londonderry_p.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Queen? Is this someone from British history? </speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">But what queen would be blindfolded … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">It couldn't be just some ignorant rambling nonsense … </speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmm … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Is it some kind of metaphor? Like “John the Baptist” or “Mary Antoinette”?</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19Bg4sTQmgcZy8IrP4i">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">Both were beheaded and killed. In particular the death of John the Baptist is legendary for its extremely “beautiful” (read: sick and gratuitous*) description by Oscar Wilde (1854-1900) in his play “Salome” — </p>
                <p class="article-text">“Ah! thou wouldst not suffer me to kiss thy mouth, Iokanaan [John]. Well! I will kiss it now. I will bite it with my teeth as one bites a ripe fruit. Yes, I will kiss thy mouth, Iokanaan. I said it; did I not say it? I said it. Ah! I will kiss it now … But wherefore dost thou not look at me, Iokanaan? ” (*Translator's note: The Chinese word used here is 病娇, which is a loanword from Japanese ヤンデレ or “Yandere”) </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">John the Baptist? Mary Antoinette? What do you mean?</speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmm … I was just speaking nonsense. Don't mind me. Don't mind me at all.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It's not like I have a fetish for Wildean aesthetics or anything. </speak> <!-- 图腾 = loanword from the English "totem"-->
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … I don't understand at all. I am absolutely confused. </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Correct.</speak>
            <text>Staying aloof from the awkward atmosphere brewing between the two, Mophead appears to arrive at an epiphany, suddenly bringing her hands together into a single clap.</text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace" remark="next">“The Execution of Lady Jane Grey”. </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">“The Execution of Lady Jane Grey” is an oil painting by Paul Delaroche (1797-1865), showing the historical tale of Lady Jane Grey (1537-1554) being deposed and executed at the age of 16. </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaStarGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah … ! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">There is indeed such a painting! The subject of the painting — Queen Jane Grey — she is blindfolded, about to be executed by an executioner! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaSmileGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It seems that we may be spending the night on a boat. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> — Tomorrow we shall be making a visit to the National Gallery. </speak>
            <goto goto="40" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="trafalgarSquare.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_PeerGynt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The next day. </text>
            <text>Ascending slowly up a flight of steps, and leaving Charing Cross Underground Station via a narrow exit, the group find themselves greeted by that iconic landmark of the Empire — Trafalgar Square. </text>
            <text>Perhaps symbolic of the fact that “the Sun never sets on the Empire”, even on a cold wintry Monday, there is no shortage of tourists. </text>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">So this is the centre of Greater London … </speak>
            <text>Looking at Nelson's Column, towering and piercing through the clouds, Welt cannot help but let out a sigh, with wonder and awe typical of a tourist. </text>
            <text>The inscription next to the memorial column indicates that it was built in honour of Admiral Horatio Nelson, the British national hero who led the Royal Navy to overwhelming victory against Napoleon's combined fleet, at the Battle of Trafalgar in 1805 — with the unfortunate cost of his own life. </text>
            <text>His resourcefulness was unsurpassed, and his valour was unmatched as the bravest of the Coalition forces — whether it was in the Atlantic, or on the Nile, or in Copenhagen, or at Trafalgar, he repeatedly led England to decisive victories. But in doing so he lost his right eye, then his right arm, and finally his own life. </text> <!-- 勇冠三军 = "the bravest of three armies", originally in reference either to the Three Kingdoms, or to the two wings and centre divisions of a single military force. -->
            <text>The British were not all crafty diplomats. They were also industrious folk, a tenacious people willing to put their lives on the line — but alas, the glory of the Empire was too dazzling, and this in turn played no small role in obscuring and concealing the individuals who made great achievements in her name.</text>
            <text remark="next">“England expects every man to do his duty.”</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX195jDOR70Cu55GKFR4g">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">“England expects that every man will do his duty.” This was the message issued by British Navy Admiral Nelson from his flagship “HMS Victory” before the start of the Battle of Trafalgar (1805). The semaphore signal is shown in the accompanying figure.</p>
                <div class="article-pic" picsrc="re_doHisDuty.jpg" style="background-position:left;height:14.4rem;"/>
                <p class="article-text"> Due to an error in the referenced memoirs, the sentence was mistakenly memorialised on Nelson's Column as “England expects every man to do his duty”.  </p>
            </remark>
            <text>Recalling Planck's warning on the plane, the young man named Welt once again makes a secret resolution to himself — </text>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> Huh? Where are the others? </speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterFar" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The art museum is to the north. </speak>
            <text>Einstein grudgingly pulls on Welt's sleeve. </text>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterFar" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Don't get lost. The items in your backpack are very important to us. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterFar" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmph. </speak>
            <text>Tesla, who has long since been dissatisfied, takes this opportunity to double-down on Welt. </text> <!--  落井下石 = "to throw stones at somebody who fell down a well". -->
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterFar" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">How can someone like you ever survive, one who is so oblivious to everything? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">I reckon, even if you train him like a pet penguin to go to the market and buy fish for you, he'll still end up getting lost. </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">Penguins can learn this behaviour in reality. Please refer to the penguin “Lala” who once lived in Shibushi, Kagoshima Prefecture, Japan. </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaSnickerGlassWinterFar" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterFar" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Ugh … </speak>
            <goto goto="45" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="45" background="trafalgarSquare.jpg">
            <bgm src="10_20_PeerGynt.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">The National Gallery sits to the north, facing south, with a set of weathered, darkened Roman columns standing across the street from Trafalgar Square — silently narrating the glorious bygone days of the old Empire. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">A heavy and profound history, laden with the sediment of life, is deposited upon the impassive architecture. This unique sense of oppression permeates through the gloomy cold haze of London, and occasionally reminds people of how formidable the violent institutions of “nationhood” and “society” can truly be. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">And the people who dealt regularly with these institutions — without the reckless bravery of Spartacus, the fierce cruelty of Robespierre, the astute wisdom of Benjamin Franklin, and the determined willpower of Vladimir Lenin — Could they have really accomplished anything at all? </p>
            </text>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey! Wake up! Yeah, it's not as good as the British Museum, but it's still worth a visit!</speak>
            <text>Not satisfied with Welt's despondent and pathetic appearance, Tesla slaps him hard on his shoulder. </text>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It's not like Tesla had said something weird. </speak>
            <text>Einstein, who is leading the way, also seems a little discontent. </text>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Huh … What weird thing!? Obviously it's the truth. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">The state of one's emotions is born from the struggle between excitement and depression. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Since you induced him towards one extreme, how can you blame him for not being at the other end?</speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … No need to speak such baffling philosophising nonsense. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It's totally not cute. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … Welt, what do you think? </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Excitement or depression, what is the essential force behind human life, or should I say “human reason”? </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Or, from the perspective of aesthetics, which one is more “cute”? </speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … ? </speak>
            <text>The young man, his mind still wandering, had clearly not paid any attention to Mophead's question — </text>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">I-I think … </speak>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">All girls are cute, no matter what they're like! </speak>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Girls are justice! </speak>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <text>For some reason, Twintail's face suddenly turns to a shade of red, then a shade of purple. </text>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Oh … </speak>
            <text> Mophead seems unconcerned with the answer, or the fact that her original question remained unanswered. </text>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">I wanted to ask Mr Welt what he thought of the “beauty of humanity” — but I'll take that as an answer. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Ugh. </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einFoolWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">What a mediocre man. </speak>
            <bgm src="10_20_PeerGynt.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <goto goto="48" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="48" background="">
            <sound src="hit man.mp3"/>
            <text>She gives him a hard flick on his forehead. </text>
            <goto goto="50" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="gallery.jpg">
            <bgm src="street.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">I didn't expect researchers like you to be interested in damaged paintings. </speak>
            <text>One of the management staff speaks, while leading the way in the rear promenade of the National Gallery. </text>
            <text>The pot-bellied, balding, obese middle-aged man is holding in his hand a wooden rack filled with hanging keys — the small metal keys clang incessantly against each other, in unison with his swaying, waddling steps. </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">A flood of the Thames in 1928 destroyed much of our collection, and even now the full extent of the damage has not been clearly appraised. </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">The only thing certain, is that the painting you're looking for is one of those in the ruined collection. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wait, you … What do you mean by “even now it has not been clearly appraised”? </speak>
            <text>The other person's statement clearly refreshed in Tesla's mind, her acute awareness of bureaucratic inefficiency. </text>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Um … After all, there are more than 2,000 world-famous paintings in this museum … </speak>
            <text>The manager splays his hands in a helpless, conceding gesture — </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">How much damage each painting has incurred can only be evaluated when the restoration is complete.  </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">You must understand … a master can only restore two or three paintings in a year. It's all quite a troublesome affair. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … So, this painting we are looking for — is it a work that is relatively low in priority for restoration? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Yes, it can be said so. After all, it is a modern work and it is difficult to rank above those other older, more “classical” works. </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Let me tell you, even the famous and most highly-esteemed Turner, has several artworks that have yet to be restored. </speak>
            <text>And in saying this, the fat balding uncle leading the group finally stops at the door of an old warehouse. </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">This is it. I'll enter with you. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hmm … </speak>
            <text>Tesla's face makes an uncomfortable expression — </text>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">We are conducting research of a most confidential nature … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">So I've heard. </speak>
            <text>The fat balding uncle does not budge — </text>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">I don't care if you're MI5 or MI6 — </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Or whatever fancy get-up — </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">But in this museum, non-staff visitors must never be left unsupervised. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">No problem. </speak>
            <text>Einstein shrugs, indicating that she does not mind. </text>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Let's go in together. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Haha, I really appreciate your cooperation. </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">At least this lady still has some common sense. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySmileClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Tsk. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I'm only cooperating for your sake — </speak>
            <bgm src="street.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAngryGlassWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wha-wha-what — What is that stench? ! </speak>
            <goto goto="60" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="storage.jpg">
            <bgm src="serenity.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>As the heavy door slowly opened with a creaking sound, a thick musty scent even heavier than the door instantly permeates into everybody's nostrils.</text>
            <text> Even Tesla, who had once visited a century-old wine cellar in Vienna, is taken aback by the pungent odour.</text>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">After a painting is affected by damp moisture, a certain amount of oil-water admixture will form on its surface … and if it is sealed in an airtight warehouse at constant temperature … </speak>
            <text> Returning the door bolt to its locked position, the fat uncle coughs a few times — </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">If you think it through: the resulting product of fermentation, I'm afraid, is not much different from swill or hogwash in terms of its composition. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Please, please don't describe it so disgustingly. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Cough cough … </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … It's “The Execution of Lady Jane Grey”, right? </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">No index cards have been made here — </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">So we can only check them by hand, one by one. </speak>
            <text>With a meek smile, the fat uncle makes a statement even more demoralising than the thick musty smell enveloping them. </text>
            <goto goto="65" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="65" background="storage.jpg">
            <bgm src="serenity.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Despite having sustained flood damage, the cultural relics are still cultural relics after all. The Fat Uncle takes great pains to shout orders so that Welt's actions can be synchronised with his own. There is still considerable weight in the picture frames — and the action of carefully lifting up and putting down each frame, repeated dozens of times, has already given both men sore hips and aching backs, their bodies dripping with sweat. </p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="70" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="storage.jpg">
            <bgm src="serenity.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="staffGalleryBlackClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:rgb(165,150,153);font-style:italic;">“The Goddess of Discord Choosing the Apple of Contention in the Garden of the Hesperides” … There are a few Turners here. Riddled with holes and scars … What a pity … </p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="75" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="75" background="storage.jpg">
            <bgm src="serenity.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaBlackGlassWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:rgb(237,118,114);font-style:italic;">“The Destruction of Pompeii and Herculaneum” … This one's already taller than me! Speaking of which, does anyone know, the one we are looking for, how big is it ?!</p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="80" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="storage2.jpg">
            <bgm src="serenity.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaBlackGlassWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:rgb(237,118,114);font-style:italic;">Uh …  this painting … will you two be okay? </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Upon seeing a work that seems to be as tall as a football goalpost, Twintails hurries forward to assist. </p>
            </text>
            <show chara="staffGalleryBlackClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:rgb(165,150,153);font-style:italic;">Miss, move a bit over there … don't be more of a hindrance than a help. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text" style="color:rgb(165,150,153);font-style:italic;">Alright, young lad … I'll count to three … One, two, three — Heave! </p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="85" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="85" background="storage2.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>A board-shaped object, larger than the warehouse door, is lifted shakily from its stand. </text>
            <text>The burlap cloth wrapped around the painting flutters about, raining down annoying puffs of dust — both hands occupied, Welt tries to hold back his sneeze, his facial features contorted to resemble a twisted pretzel. </text> <!-- In Chinese, they instead use mahua (麻花) as the metaphor - this is a northern Chinese snack made of fried dough that is also twisted in shape. -->
            <show chara="staffGallerySmileClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Alright … let's continue to remove these rags that are probably older than me … </speak>
            <text>Fat Uncle wipes the sweat from his forehead, and very carefully opens the sleeve containing the oil painting, filled with copious stains, water marks and dust. </text>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">This … This is it?! </speak>
            <goto goto="90" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG7-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeEin.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>As soon as the old sleeve cloth is peeled open, a bright ivory white comes into view of the four around the painting. </text>
            <text>Upon a dim background, an innocent girl in a white dress is blindfolded, and an old man dressed as a priest leads her towards a cruel-looking chopping block. </text> <!-- The Chinese says 断头台, or guillotine platform, whereas the painting clearly shows a more traditional chopping block. -->
            <text>This is undoubtedly “The Execution of Lady Jane Grey” — and it is in fact very well-preserved! </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Im- … Impossible … </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">How could it be possible … </speak>
            <text>The Fat Uncle, who is apparently experienced and knowledgeable in the field of fine arts, almost drops his chin for a moment. </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">My God! Not even a trace of mildew!! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">But this painting … </speak>
            <text>Evidently puzzling over other things, Twintails holds up a magnifying glass and passes around to the back of the giant painting. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … The signature area looks unchanged …  Is there anything strange about this painting? </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Why … Can't this be considered miraculous enough? </speak>
            <text>Of course Fat Uncle didn't understand what Tesla meant by “strange”. </text>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="storage2.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeEin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Do you remember where this painting was previously displayed? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Little lady, you ask about this … </speak>
            <text>Between laughter and tears, the Fat Uncle holds out his hands — </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Yet during the 1928 flood, I was nothing more than an ignorant Grammar-school student! </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaShameGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <text>Having thus understood that she was seeking information from an idiot, Tesla sticks her tongue out. </text>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Not enough clues. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Clues? </speak>
            <text>Uncle Fat is still as confused as before, his mind in a fog. </text>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … I actually have a conjecture. </speak>
            <text>From Welt's backpack, Einstein takes out a device that resembles a tube amplifier. </text>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">May I use it to scan the canvas? </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah … Could it be … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">No, it can't be … </speak>
            <text>Seeing this, Tesla also seems to realise an incredible possibility. </text>
            <show chara="teslaNormalGlassWinterClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Mmm … this “toy” of yours … it doesn't release any radiation waves, does it? </speak>
            <text>Fat Uncle stares at the suspicious device with a guarded expression. </text>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace" remark="next">It just emits microwaves in a specific band. It has no destructive power. </speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19HAOD7GN9woHXyw4Jp">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">According to quantum theory, the ability of electromagnetic waves to affect molecules depends on their frequency (or wavelength). The higher the frequency (or, the shorter the wavelength), the greater its ability to alter molecular structures. </p>
                <p class="article-text">In particular, as a kind of far-infrared electromagnetic wave, the frequency of the microwave is far from sufficient to change the molecule itself, so an object will merely be heated when exposed to microwave radiation — a property that is exploited in the microwave oven. </p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It will induce the activation of a certain rare element, and cause it to separate from its original mixed state. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Oh … </speak>
            <text>For a moment, Fat Uncle reacts with nothing more than rubbing his balding forehead. </text>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Wait … Are you going to use that toy to squeeze or draw something out of this canvas?! </speak>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It can be understood as such. </speak>
            <show chara="einSmileWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">No, no, no! If I let you do that, wouldn't the painting be ruined?! </speak>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … Unlikely. </speak>
            <text>Mophead takes out a flashlight from her pocket, and shines it on the canvas from the side, at an angle. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Indeed. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Huh? </speak>
            <text>Fat Uncle remains oblivious. </text>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Please observe carefully. </speak>
            <text>The young girl explains while maintaining the angle of the flashlight. </text>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Do you see? On the surface of the painting, there is a thin film. </speak>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryNormalClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … Hmm … Protective lacquer? </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">No, there is no protective lacquer that is able to keep a painting in such a pristine state! </speak>
            <text>Fat Uncle's expression becomes even more confused. On careful inspection, it can be noticed that the film even has a slight metallic sheen! </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … What is … this? </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … I have never seen or heard of such a thing! </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">If you permit, we can test it now. </speak>
            <text>Mophead begins cranking the handle of the machine in her arms. </text>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … I said that you are not allowed to damage the picture! </speak>
            <text> Fat Uncle suddenly becomes anxious — </text>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">If we pull some kind of nonsense, you and I will all be deemed sinners against humanity! </speak> <!-- 幺蛾子 = "To cause small moths to appear", northern Chinese phrase for "creating problems", much like how moths could wreak havoc on food stores. -->
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … You are being overly dramatic. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">After we're done, this painting …  will simply become as fragile as the other “normal” collections. </speak>
            <show chara="einNormalWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">This substance on the painting is very important to us. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">To just let it sit here, merely protecting a painting, may be a huge waste of its value. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBoringGlassWinterClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose-up" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">If you continue to refuse us, our organisation will make use of other options. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I don't mean to bring ill tidings … but when that moment comes, I fear that you and your staff will find that you've bitten off more than you can chew. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaEmbarraGlassWinterClose-up" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … Ugh. </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySweatClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Little lady, I am not blind to reason. </speak>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">But even if the procedure is “non-destructive” to the painting itself, I believe there is one thing you still need to explain clearly  … </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace">Once you've extracted that thin film, what value is there in it? From an ethical point of view, why should our art museum allow you to do such a thing? </speak>
            <show chara="staffGallerySeriousClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">To foretell the fate of humanity. </speak>
            <text>Mophead speaks in a icy-cold voice like never before. </text>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose-up" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left"/>
            <shake position="left" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="nekoNoFace"> … ? ! </speak>
            <show chara="staffGalleryScareClose-up" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <hide position="right"/>
            <show chara="einSeriousEmWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <text>Before Uncle Manager could recover from his dumbstruck state, Einstein has already aimed the machine at the centre of the canvas. </text>
            <show chara="einSeriousAhWinterClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Initiating resonant-form Soulium extraction. </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Everybody, please cover your ears. </speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX19TjZQmi9wqji9OWE3F"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
