<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story title="1">
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="newchapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="studyLamp.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">In the four weeks beginning from now, the lab assistant named Welt will be bearing a heavy responsibility. Lab 42 is now on a “quasi-holiday” because the supercomputer Ada has been shackled with a computationally-heavy task — which means Welt needs to organise recreational activities for the two doctors every day for the entire period. Although one of the doctors proclaims that “Just because we're on vacation, doesn't mean we don't need to work some days”; given the personality of the other doctor, it seems difficult to say for certain what the workload is going to be like for Welt … </p>
            </text>
            <text>Especially given that just a few hours earlier, his own foolhardy behaviour had caused her to blow a fuse.</text> <!--  无腦耍帅 = "to be brainless while trying to act brave and cool"; 火冒三丈 = "to burn with a rage that extends thirty feet" -->
            <text>The wall clock silently ticks past eleven o'clock. Despite knowing that the community safety in this neighbourhood is one of the best in Britain, Welt remains uneasy, and since he has trouble sleeping anyway, chooses to stay up all night in the lobby. </text>
            <text>On the other hand, Einstein, who seems accustomed to her roommate's late-night adventures, had already gone upstairs to “rest” an hour ago. </text>
            <sound src="8_24_mess.mp3"/>
            <text> — If not for the various sounds of falling debris in the garbage chute, occurring from time to time. It sounds like someone taking this opportunity to finally clean up the house.</text>
            <text remark="next">After drinking his seventh cup of black tea, the “Catcher in the Rye” in his hand has already been flipped to its last page. </text>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">“The Catcher in the Rye” is a novel published by American writer JD Salinger in 1951.  </p>
                <p class="article-text"> When it was first published, many schools and libraries banned the book; but now, this book is a designated reading for many American schools. Some critics say that it “has greatly affected generations of American youth.” </p>
            </remark>
            <text>The silly protagonist of the book had an amusing temperament, and this reminded him of “Don Quixote” he had read last year. </text>
            <text>Ah. </text>
            <text>Speaking of which … </text>
            <text>Just now he had received a letter, and it was a very strange letter indeed … </text>
            <goto goto="15" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="15" background="CG9-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_3_themeOtto.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="CG9-1.jpg"></cg>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text-h">Ω: </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">When you do receive this letter, it should already be around the 31st. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">Happy Halloween. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I heard that, because a certain Overseer pays special attention to this festival, I've had to make grand arrangements at Headquarters every year … Yes, the attached photo shows the state of my preparations this year. </p>
                <p class="article-text">By the way, something else to “celebrate”: starting this month, my lab's staff has been reduced to just me alone — so as you can see, even when taking a team photo, I can only take one of myself. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I haven’t heard from you recently. Is it because of the new opportunities that have rekindled your passion for life? I've heard you guys have been travelling back and forth between the Atlantic Ocean, and have been having a great time. However, the North American branch has always been rated poorly by Headquarters. If they happen to cause some sort of trouble amongst themselves, or be at loggerheads with each other, you mustn't blindly participate … I've heard that still water runs deep, and thing can get rather treacherous. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text"> … But I'm also being stupid. When Gods fight, what does it matter to mere mortals like you and me?  Best not talk about it any more. Now, I don't know what the weather is like in London — but the moonlight in Vienna tonight is indeed hard to come by; I will thus borrow the power of alcohol to guide us in a casual chat, about some things we cannot usually talk about. Well, it's a letter, so just let me talk, and you can just listen — don't take any of this too seriously. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I know that you are a person who likes reading. But … have you ever thought about what has caused us human beings, in our struggle against the Honkai, to be repeatedly thwarted, to suffer loss after loss? After all, what flaws make us vulnerable to constant forestalling by the Honkai, to the point that we are close to complete surrender, too tired to cope anymore? </p>
                <p class="article-text">In other words … why do we always, always, always repeat the same mistakes? </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">It is true that, throughout human history, we have been steadily progressing, and this trend of progress will unlikely be obstructed by any trivial event or matter; but what I've been seeing more, are those pioneers who stand on the crest of the wave — isolated and cut off from help, battered and bruised, caught between a rock and a hard place. Sometimes, they may even lose, defeated and embarrassed by their own human foibles. Spiritually, they may be giants, but sometimes physically or materially they are weaklings; their spiritual strength often takes a long time to be passed down to later generations, before they are eventually recognised as cherished paragons. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Earlier, I told you the story of Saint Kallen. However, what I want to say today is … Despite her strong force of character, nature instead granted her the body of an ordinary girl (although the bloodline of Kaslana is definitely nothing ordinary … but that won't make much difference to what I'm about to say here) — a body so weak and frail, one so minuscule and insignificant, that even the common folk can sentence her to death, so that even a lowly Honkai beast can take her life with ease. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Doesn't this make absolutely no sense? </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">The world we live in, it does not follow logic at all, and it does not respect the principle of equivalent exchange! </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I will never forget what Kallen experienced during her brief life. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">I am convinced that, for us humans, the greatest enemy is not the Honkai at all, but ourselves. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text"> — We are too weak, so weak that our heroes are always powerless to save everyone; we are too weak, so weak that some of us would even doubt the motives of our heroes; we are too weak, so weak that we will sacrifice true justice for a small immediate gain; we are too weak, so weak that we can only negotiate short-term peace amidst mutual conflict, and that we have to resort to official, pompous-sounding words like “social order” and “ethics” to cover up our despicable motives. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">The Saint … She is a Saint because, despite being as fragile as us, she is very different from us, for she is one — just the one, the only one — who does not fear her vulnerability. This kind of bravery, emanating from the heart, is like the sun to us ordinary folk — something we can all see, but can clearly never attain. </p>
                <p class="article-text">At least, compared to her … I am a complete coward. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Every one of us, harbouring this original sin called “fear”, trepidly seeks the answers to life's questions. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">The Saint would never deride or jeer at us. But every time I realise we are living like this, I wish that I could kill myself with a single blow. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">But imagine, if, if each of us really has a chance to rid ourselves of this fragility; if we can uproot this fear, this thought of “I am fragile” deeply rooted within our hearts … then we can create a new culture at that moment, one that is full of forgiveness, full of self-confidence, and full of vigour! And then this so-called “Honkai”, won't it then dwindle to something so small, so insignificant, as to be unworthy of further mention? </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">Such a world, would protect its own Saints. </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text">Such a world, is more worthy of protection from its Saints. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">If, if, if there is ever a chance that Kallen is able to shine upon this world stage again, then, this time, she will not struggle to progress because of our own meagreness. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I haven't tasted red wine for a long time, but I have really been drinking quite a bit today. In your opinion, this letter may be pure unintelligible incoherent rambling … but this doesn't matter. Before, I had been talking to you as a member of the organisation; today, let me be an ordinary researcher, and let me have a casual, self-opinionated rant for once. </p>
            </text>
            <text article="1">
                <p class="article-text">I don't think the kind of world I have just imagined can be realised … but it doesn't matter. We still have a lot to do — don't we? </p>
                <br />
                <p class="article-text-s">Your old friend, who has been acting a little strange today, </p>
                <p class="article-text-s">Clown Alpha</p>
                <p class="article-text-s">1955.10.28.</p>
            </text>
            <goto goto="30" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="studyLamp.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeWelt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The hour hand on the wall clock has moved 60°, and it is already early morning of the next day. </text>
            <text>Welt silently refills his eighth cup of black tea. </text>
            <sound src="11_3_mess lock.mp3"/>
            <text>Click. </text>
            <sound src="11_3_mess lock.mp3"/>
            <text>Click click. </text>
            <sound src="11_3_mess lock.mp3"/>
            <text>Click click click. </text>
            <text>At last, outside the door, there is that familiar sound unique to drunkards: the sound of a prodding key from one who cannot, for the life of them, find the keyhole to the lock. </text>
            <goto goto="40" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="studyNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah … you little dječak … not asleep, I see. </speak>
            <text>Drifting footsteps, breath full of alcohol — there is no doubt, this woman has already drunk more than enough. </text>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Yes. Do you want to go upstairs? </speak>
            <text> Thinking back to Mophead's advice, the young man decides to deal with the situation with an ordinary, calm mindset. </text>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Upstairs?  … Ne, ne. </speak>
            <text>The red-haired woman with half-loosened twintails waves both hands dismissively. </text>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You … you come and talk to me. </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … M-me? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">None … None of that n-nonsense! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">If not you … who else is there … hmm? </speak>
            <goto goto="50" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="CG9-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>The “clearly sober adult” seizes the opportunity to flop down and sprawl all over the small sofa beside him. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … You haven't heard of it anyway, have you? </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Haven't heard? </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Uh … Haven't heard of what? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … You're being wordy today, aren't you. Are you a visiting member from the House of Commons? If you haven't heard of it, then you haven't heard of it, da? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … Okay, this old gal is gonna use this rare occasion to explain it to you, so you better wash your ears and listen like the good little dječak you are, okay? </speak>
            <text>The red-haired drunkard continues to ramble incessantly, while she scornfully flings her coat over the back of the sofa. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … You know, this old gal's name is Nikola. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It just happens to be a girl's name as well, so I use it like that. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">However, on the passport … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ha ha ha ha ha, speaking of it now, I feel a bit embarrassed. </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Uh … Are you trying to say … </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … that Nikola is a pseudonym? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Actually … no, it's not a pseudonym. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Frederica Nikola Tesla … That's my full name. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Really, it sounds like a name for a German sow. </speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19IgpxWjGoRkLC6kAMe">
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">Tesla is a Serbian who was born in Croatia and has Austrian nationality. In Central and Eastern Europe, this is not uncommon for historical reasons. </p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Um … isn't that … a rather cute name? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … Tsk. </speak>
            <text>Dissatisfied, the drunkard shifts her posture, and crosses her legs together — </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I knew you men would speak like that. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">A unisex name like Nikola, and you men immediately lose interest, aren't I right? </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Uh … i-it isn't really like that … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I've had enough of a life that treats me as a simple, ordinary “girl”. </speak>
            <text>The drunkard's speech suddenly speeds up dramatically — </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">The whole thing's so stupid, I think I might just die from the stupid. How can human personality be defined by such boring things as gender and race? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Have their brains been soaked with formalin? </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text"> Formalin is a mixed aqueous solution with a formaldehyde content of about 40% and a methanol content of about 15%. It is generally used as a preservative for specimen preparation.</p>
                <p class="article-text"> In our world, on April 18, 1955, within 7 hours of the death of physicist Albert Einstein, his brain was preliminarily fixed with a 10% to 11.4% formalin solution, and then preserved for histological sectioning. </p>
            </remark>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … But indeed, unfortunately, the vast majority of people in the world can only confine themselves in these little cocoons, planning their lives around senseless labels. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">As soon as someone steps out of these black-and-white “rules”, they'll become inexplicably angry, and get all riled up, as if their lives were completely ruined. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">These people probably forget that these various identities within us, are all just fabricated values, created by humans to organise society into an orderly state. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Everything that does not exist in the natural world is nothing more than personal assumption, nothing more than human fabrication.</speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Fa-bri-ca-tion! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Schicksal is fabricated, Britain is fabricated, driving on the left is fabricated, even the toilet being divided into ladies and gents — that too is fabricated! </speak>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Urgh … </speak>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="studyNight.jpg">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace" remark="next">Ah … Izvini, izvini, I'm speaking too much at once, it's almost like I'm stuffing a goose. </speak>
            <remark>
                <p class="article-text-h">Note: </p>
                <p class="article-text">Foie gras (“fat liver”) is a famous French dish, often called “geese liver” in Chinese (鹅肝), when in fact, duck liver can also used as the raw ingredient. </p>
                <p class="article-text">Foie gras farms force ducks or geese to develop fatty livers by tube-feeding food directly into their stomachs. Gavage is carried out for 2 to 4 weeks, 2 to 3 times a day, when a specially-prepared slurry of feed is directly poured into the oesophagus using a tube. This will cause a large amount of excess nutrients to accumulate in its liver, resulting in an enlarged and delicate fatty liver. </p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Guess I'm Nikola Tesla, with a doctorate in “post-alcohol verbosity”. </speak>
            <text>The redhead half-rises from her seat, snatches the black tea in front of the young man, and without any warning, drinks it down in one gulp.  </text>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">All of you call me a doctor — but I haven't even graduated yet, have I? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Huh? </speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Are you so surprised … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">It's not uncommon for people to defer or leave school for various reasons. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">But … aren't you doing research here? </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah, this is different. </speak>
            <text>Tesla shrugs languidly. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Professor Planck is purely theoretical with her work — with my current research, I can't graduate under her supervision. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Especially Einstein that bitch … recently she's only willing to let me run “virtual” tests on Ada! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Only because I'd blown up the bedroom once or twice before … Isn't that a bit excessive? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Oh. </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Do you know who Ada is? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … If we're talking about Ada, I'd just met her today. </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Rawr — looks like you've already analysed the stuff in  the toy? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">No … Looks like it'll take at least four weeks to produce results. </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hic … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Then tonight we shall pull an all-nighter and play till dawn! Ahahahahaha! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">A-all-nighter? </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaLveDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ain't that so … Of course, silly! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Four weeks! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaLveDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">A whole month! Don't you understand?! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ada is going to be busy for four weeks, so how am I … how am I going to refuse this big vacation? </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">HAHAHAHAHAHA! Holiday time! A life of luxury and debauchery! HERE I COME! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">What are you waiting for, boy, bring your gal some wine! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="left" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">H-hey  … You … Y-you shouldn't be drinking any more, should you? </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">You're already in such a drunken state …  and still you want to drink more?! </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hic. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Saying such stupid things …  I'd say that you've been the one having too much to drink … HAHAHAHA! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaLveDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Wasn't that a super-snappy response? I can definitely go for another round! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Since you refuse to help … </speak>
            <hide position="left"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … then how about I go help myself? </speak>
            <goto goto="120" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="corridorMessy.jpg">
            <bgm src="lab.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>As she speaks, she sways and wobbles towards upstairs. </text>
            <text>Her goal is obvious — the plump, gaudy refrigerator at the end of the corridor on the top floor. </text>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Ah … No, no! </speak>
            <text> Seeing that he cannot block Tesla's steps, Welt crosses his heart and rushes forward to hold her tightly. </text>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … Hey! What are you doing! </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> Let go of my hand! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">If you're going to keep drinking, I'm not going to let go. </speak>
            <text> The young man takes a step forward and grabs her other hand. </text>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ha? Finally, after much difficulty, I've managed to secure a holiday, how can I not be permitted to enjoy my freedom? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaLveDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Are you really going to stop me from getting another drink, you grinch?! </speak>
            <text>The drunk is obviously dissatisfied with Welt's rough interference — she flicks her hands up and down like a skipping rope, trying to break free from Welt. </text> <!-- The original Chinese used specific imagery: 拉面大师 = a chef expert in making Chinese "pulled noodles", more commonly known in Japanese as "ramen" (ラーメン); see \href{https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6Ge1_eJq7RY}{this link} at 0:20 for the imagery. Changed to a skipping rope motion to avoid confusion. -->
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Hey! </speak>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Pervert! Sexual deviant! </speak>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Let go now! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">You must let go! Let go! Let go! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Are you able to behave responsibly and look after your own body, in this state? </speak>
            <text>The young man does not know whether he should laugh or cry — the red-haired girl, whose hands he is holding, is now lying on the ground, breaking out into a tantrum. She is flinging about and causing a scene, just like a toddler who is refused her toy. </text>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … You won't let go, won't you. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaBiteDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Before you give up your quest for more alcohol …  No, I-I cannot let go!</speak>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">You're drunk. Go back to your room and rest. </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">No! I'm not drunk! I am clearly sober! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Only a drunk would say that! </speak>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaNormalDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Not drunk, not drunk means I'm not drunk! </speak>
            <text>Tesla squats angrily on the ground — then all of a sudden, she violently leaps up as though an idea has hopped into her mind. </text>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">I know. I won't drink anymore. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Don't lie to me. </speak>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Not lying! Not lying! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <text>The bundle of red hair, exuding the scent of wine, flashes a impish grin. </text>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">But, for a price … </speak>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace"> … you'll have to play with me! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Play with me, then I won't drink! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Really! Really! I'm not lying to you! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaAstonishDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … </speak>
            <show chara="weltNormalWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> … Okay. </speak>
            <text>In the face of Death, the young man nods — </text>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">So, what are you planning to play? It's late at night, you know? </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ha ha ha ha, what is fun to play late at night? </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltSurpriseWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Huh? </speak>
            <show chara="weltScaredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">D-Don't say such dangerous things! </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace"> H-hearing you say such things is practically the same as being guilty of doing it?! </speak>
            <show chara="weltTiredWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Ah. So shy. So timid. </speak>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">Shy, timid, stop speaking nonsense! </speak>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="weltNoFace">How am I shy! </speak>
            <show chara="weltShameWinterClose" position="right" opacity="0.7"/>
            <show chara="teslaFoolDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">H-h-h-hey, I'm just going to say it then! </speak>
            <show chara="teslaLveDrunkWinterClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="teslaNoFace">Welt! You stinky boy! If you have the courage, come and — </speak>
            <goto goto="130" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="">
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <text>Bam. </text>
            <goto goto="140" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="140" background="corridorMessy.jpg">
            <bgm src="themeTesla.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>From the shadows behind them, a dictionary comes flying out and hits the noisy woman squarely on the head. </text>
            <show chara="0einSeriousAhVestClose-up" position="center"/>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">It's the middle of the night and you're loud as hell! </speak>
            <shake position="center" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> Let me get some sleep! Now! Right now! </speak>
            <show chara="0einNormalVestClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> … </speak>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> …  … </speak>
            <show chara="0einFoolVestClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace"> …  …  … </speak>
            <show chara="einBagaVestClose-up" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="einNoFace">Say, Welt … why is she suddenly so still? </speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX19e4WHxF4Pk4HxRATs2"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>	



