<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_12_mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="11_12_newChapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="10" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="10" background="beachAzores.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>When Shakespeare and her companions returned from the 「funeral」, the rest of the crew had finished setting up a simple stage next to the Caledonia under Lalla's orders.</text>
            <text>The red haired captain gathered everyone there and prepared herself to make a speech.</text>
            <goto goto="20" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="CG12-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Cough.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">As you all know, I'm not the type to adhere to formalities.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">In a certain story Antony's silver tongue alone was enough to turn Caesar into an enemy but——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——Compared to those brilliant dictators and assassins, I'm just a clown bearing the evil of history.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Oops, I digress. I will now tell you all the purpose of this trip.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Our next destination is the Yucatan Peninsula. There lies a jewel, or should I say part, of a weapon capable of saving the world.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Needless to say, we'll look for ways to make ourselves rich as usual.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">I'm sure there will be plenty of opportunities to make money in this continent many can't travel to.</speak>
            <goto goto="30" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="CG12-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">...But now that we're departing from our good old continent——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——As your Captain, there are some things I must tell you.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">The motivation behind this unprecedented, long distance voyage.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">We'll cross the Atlantic and Pacific, and step on many foreign lands.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">The reason for that goes beyond money and honor.</speak>
            <goto goto="40" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="CG12-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">I've always said you all are pirates of the 「Caledonia」 but also members of the 「King's Men」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——I never said those words because I missed my old business or because I wanted to make you all take part in a play one day.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——The true meaning of those words is,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">The world is the greatest stage of all, and those who enjoy their lives are the greatest actors!</speak>
            <goto goto="50" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="CG12-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">We are pirates. Like all pirates, what we want is one simple thing: 「Freedom」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">There are no annoying laws to bind us on the sea. We take everything, we share everything, we live the way we want.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">However—— Those days will soon come to an end.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Why, you ask? Because there is a rope around our necks, tightening more and more each day.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">That invisible rope has already claimed the lives of many tutelary deities.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Their names were——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">England,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Scotland,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Ireland,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">France,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Netherlands,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Germany,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Scandinavia,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Poland,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Bohemia,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Hungary,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Wallachia,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Bulgaria,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Serbia,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Albania,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Greece,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Italy,</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">And Iberia.</speak>
            <goto goto="60" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="CG12-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">...Some of you may have heard of them.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">All of them form 「Europe」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">A continent that used to be prosperous and free under the blessing of the Gods.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">That place was truly Arcadia, the golden land.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——But that's not the case anymore.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">As we all saw when we crossed the Mediterranean, Europe is currently blocked by invincible tall walls. The continent has become an inhabitable place no one can set foot on.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">There is a legend that speaks of the beginning of this tragedy——</speak>
            <goto goto="70" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="CG12-2.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「On the day of the autumnal equinox, the Emperor landed on Amsterdam.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">To this day I still don't know who this 「Emperor」 is, but the way he ruled his nation was unlike anything we've ever seen.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">The elders said: 「The Emperor of a foreign land took his servants and swarmed the streets. Then, strange things started to happen.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「Half of those who saw them couldn't help but join them, as if they were born to be the Emperor's servants.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「The Emperor's servants didn't eat, dink nor sleep. They just followed their Emperor, singing songs in a strange language and marching forward.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「They crossed mountains and rivers until they arrived at the ruins of an ancient city at the center of the continent.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「We don't know what the Emperor did there, but the ruins were suddenly overflowing with energy and the mirror-like walls began to spread infinitely.」</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">「It was like all the world's fire and lightning was located inside those walls. Everything that came in contact with them, be it people, animals or plants, evaporated into pale dust.」</speak>
            <goto goto="80" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="CG12-3.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">That's what your ancestors experienced.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">A century later, these walls no one could lay a finger on caged the entirety of Europe.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——I'm sure everyone remembers the tragedy of Gibraltar from 5 years ago.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">No one can guess what kind of calamity awaits us next...</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">...Until someone defeats that natural disaster, until someone steals back the world from the hands of the so-called 「Emperor」.</speak>
            <goto goto="90" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="CG12-4.jpg">
            <bgm src="12_14_moonLight.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Listen, men! We are pirates! What else could be more exciting than stealing the world!?</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Let's go an epic adventure that will make our descendants jealous!</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Of course, I'm aware we're only human, we can't afford to be reckless.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Fortunately for us, the opportunity to turn the tide to our favor has appeared before us.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Come on, traveler who hides behind an iron mask, Professor who came from another world! It's time for you to speak of the day our destinies crossed 30 years ago!</speak>
            <goto goto="100" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="beachAzores.jpg">
            <bgm src="05_01_themeEin.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>The Captain pointed her finger at 「Iron Mask」, who then took off her mask and showed everyone her face for the first time.</text>
            <text>The sword Durandal she was holding in her hand read the mood and returned to its original form.</text>
            <goto goto="110" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="110" background="CG12-5.jpg">
            <bgm src="05_01_themeEin.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Ironface">Hello, everyone.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Ironface">I am Erwin Reanna Schrodinger. Due to certain reasons I've been hiding my identity until now.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">The Captain asked me to tell you about my past, so I'll take this opportunity to tell a little story.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Unlike most of you, I left my world out of my own volition.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Same as our two newcomer Valkyries over there.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">To be specific, we belong to the same world, and even the same organization.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...This happened a few decades ago.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">One day I was involved in a certain accident.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">It resulted in the loss of my 「stability」 as a physical entity.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">As such, the imaginary energy went out of control, and the unitarity of my quantum distribution was altered——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">The people of that world call this phenomenon:</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">「Quantization」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">My entity disappeared and my consciousness fell to the bottom of the 「Quantum Sea」, the world of lowest energy where I would be trapped forever...</speak>
            <bgm src="12_14_Sonnet_18.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...Or I was supposed to.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I was lucky enough to find this holy sword that also came from the outside world while I was slowly sinking into the abyss.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">The holy sword at the time didn't have a soul, it was just a piece of metal. In contrast, I was a soul without body.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Thanks to that difference I was able to stabilize my own existence, and by coming in contact with me, the holy sword was able to regain its former strength.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Together we were able to pour enough energy to make a leap out of the abyss.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">But we were too far away from our original world——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">——There was no 「beacon」 to guide us back to our world. As such, we were unable to specify a landing point and had to 「leap」 blindly.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...And as you all can see, we arrived 「here」, albeit in an incomplete state.</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I don't believe in things like fate, but I'm convinced there is something only this sword can do in this irregular world——</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">——That is, to tear down the walls of calamity that threaten humanity.</speak>
            <bgm src="11_15_shakespeareTheme.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger" remark="next">...Captain, may I borrow the 「Great Star of Africa」?</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX19iXpOj+BlU3UoHLW2y">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">“非洲之星”是库里南钻石（Cullinan Diamond）的一个别称。这颗钻石是人类迄今发现的最大天然钻石原石，重3106克拉（约相当于621克）。</p>
                <p class="article-text">英帝国政府于1907年得到该钻石后，命宝石匠将它切割成了9大块（及许多小块），以便进一步雕琢加工。其中最大的一块（530.2克拉）被镶嵌在王室权杖的顶部，次大的一块（317.4克拉）则被镶嵌在帝国皇冠的正面。</p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="120" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="beachAzores.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_15_shakespeareTheme.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <show chara="shakesQuestionClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Wait! Are you planning to use it to do 「that」?</speak>
            <show chara="shakesQuestionClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...You don't want to sell it anyway.</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesPityClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">.....</speak>
            <show chara="shakesSweatyClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">...F-Fine. I suppose all jewels no matter how precious are destined to be cut.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">At least cut it nicely, okay?</speak>
            <goto goto="130" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="beachAzores.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_15_shakespeareTheme.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <text>10 minutes later, a rough diamond, about the size of an eggplant, was brought from the Captain's room.</text>
            <text>Its size was certainly amazing. As far as its surface is concerned, it was closer to glass rather than a diamond.</text>
            <text>——Just by touching it with a hand one can tell it's the world's purest crystal, its smooth texture quickly adapted to the temperature of the palm.</text>
            <text>While everyone was busy fawning over the diamond, Schrodinger placed the holy sword upside down in the center of the table.</text>
            <text>Her right hand holding the hilt was glowing purple, as if it was pouring energy into the sword.</text>
            <text>「I'm ready」 she said. She extended her left hand towards the man behind her, and told him 「bring me the diamond」.</text>
            <text>She held the world's most precious jewel gently, as if she was a potter molding a clay pot, a carpenter using a plane.</text>
            <text>She put the jewel next to the sword, and gently but steadily began to rub it, like putting margarine on a slice of bread.</text>
            <text>When Schrodinger lifted the sword for inspection, the section where 「margarine was put」 was smooth and clear.</text>
            <text>While the sailors hold their breath, Schrodinger spins the diamond, as if she was peeling a potato.</text>
            <text>And lastly she returned the jewel that was cut to the captain.</text>
            <text>「This isn't my area of expertise, so the only thing I could do was to keep the size of the stone as small as possible.」</text>
            <text>「...I hope the diamond didn't lose its value.」</text>
            <text>With an expressionless face, Schrodinger pulled the sword out of the table, causing the light to disappear.</text>
            <text>She promptly left the stage and returned to her seat.</text>
            <goto goto="140" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="140" background="submarineCabinBlur.jpg">
            <bgm src="peerGynt.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="shakesBagaLeftClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">What a wonderful performance, Professor Schrodinger!</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">You got me worried for a moment there, I thought the 「Great Star of Africa」 was going to be split in two!</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I would had done that if I didn't know better and know you would ask to be compensated later.</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...Anyway, Valkyries—— It seems there is something you've been wanting to say for a while.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Feel free to say it now.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">....</speak>
            <show chara="biancaShyClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">Umm...</speak>
            <show chara="biankaChayaoClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">A-Are you that Schrodinger, the one from the famous 「dead but also alive」 thing?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaChayaoClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...Excuse me?</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="rita17SquintClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Rita">...I think Bianka-sama is referring to the 「cat that is both alive and dead」 experiment.</speak>
            <show chara="rita17SquintClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...Ah, that silly thing.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">That silly thought experiment is what comes first to people's minds when they think of me?</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaSurpriseClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Eh?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">S-Silly? 「Schrodinger's Cat」 is very popular, you know?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaHesitateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">It's just a dumb example of a paradox.</speak>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I have no clue why it became so popular.</speak>
            <show chara="schroMemoryClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...</speak>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">.....</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Nevermind that. This isn't the time to be talking about the past.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Feel free to think whatever you want about my past. What matters now is solving this world's biggest problem.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="rita17NormalClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Rita">(.....)</speak>
            <show chara="rita17NormalClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...Actually, I have one hypothesis regarding that. I have no proof of it, but I feel like I should tell you about it.</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaSeriousClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaSeriousClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">I theorize the 「bubble world」 we are in right now has a life span—— And that it is much shorter than the life span of a 「regular」 world.</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">If that's the case, we need to hurry.</speak>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Seeing as how the owner of those 「walls」 don't seem interested in the outside world, it might be possible they don't know about it.</speak>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaAngryClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">You mean...</speak>
            <show chara="biankaAngryClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Of course, this is just my speculation. There is no evidence to deny it, but neither to confirm it.</speak>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">It may even be possible the people inside the 「walls」 are traveling back and forth to the outside world.</speak>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <bgm src="12_29_busyHarbor.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Hahaha! Rather than worrying about that, we should be worrying about the weather outside!</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">The weather? Is there a storm coming?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesSweatyClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">No, I'm talking about something else.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Our next destination is a tropical zone. Don't you think it'll be suffocating to be wearing these clothes in that kind of weather?</speak>
            <show chara="shakesConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Always thinking ahead, your brilliant Captain has prepared new clothes for the occasion——</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——Now, strip and put them on!</speak>
            <show chara="shakesLaughClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaSurpriseClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaChayaoClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">H-Hey! Don't just throw them at me! Besides, there is no way I can change right here! Also, these clothes——</speak>
            <show chara="biankaChayaoClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesBagaLeftClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">No problem, we just have to make all the men leave the room.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesBagaLeftClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaBiteClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">.....</speak>
            <show chara="biankaBiteClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="rita17SquintClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Rita">Don't worry, Bianka-sama. I will act as your wall.</speak>
            <show chara="rita17SquintClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaChayaoClose" position="right"/>
            <shake position="right" time="250"></shake>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Rita! That's not the problem here!!</speak>
            <goto goto="150" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="150" background="black">
            <bgm src="12_29_busyHarbor.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">T-These clothes... are they the correct size?</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">There is no problem. You look great, Bianka-sama.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">...Don't say another word, Rita. More importantly... Hey, Captain! Your new clothes are practically the same as the old ones!!</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">Of course, I am the Captain. It'll be a problem if the sailors don't recognize me at first glance.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">Ah, if the ship gets too hot I should make everyone work in swimsuits.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">...What are you saying!?</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">Just so you know, I'm not taking part on that.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">Ah, right. Schrodinger-san doesn't need to regulate her body temperature.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">——It's all about being stylish. A 「Valkyrie」 should be wearing pretty, cute clothes! This is the perfect opportunity, it would be such a waste otherwise.</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">S-Stop saying weird things! And I think you misunderstood what Valkyries are!—— Agh! Rita! What...</speak>
            <speak chara="_SomeOneTalking">The size doesn't seem to be a problem. Next it's the skirt...</speak>
            <goto goto="160" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="160" background="submarineCabinBlur.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_29_lab.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="shakesCasualConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Heh, it does look great on you.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualConfidentClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Y-You think so?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="ritaVestNaughtyClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Rita">Yes. Specially that ribbon. It looks very cute.</speak>
            <show chara="ritaVestNaughtyClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">.....</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShyClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesCasualLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Now that everyone is ready let's start the 「live stream」 right away.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualLaughClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...L-Live stream!?</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroCalmClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">...It's just a wireless video call.</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">The other day I was told to set up a communication channel between the Caledonia and Alexandria.</speak>
            <show chara="schroTalkClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">——Here we go.</speak>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <text>Turururu...</text>
            <show chara="AliceSurprisedCloseE" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Alice">Hello, Professor Schrodinger. Are you all already crossing the Atlantic Ocean?</speak>
            <show chara="AliceSurprisedCloseE" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Schrodinger">Yes. Is Shelley busy right now?</speak>
            <show chara="schroSmileClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="AliceSmileCloseE" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Alice">She's in the study, should I call her?</speak>
            <show chara="AliceSmileCloseE" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesCasualConfidentClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">Nah, it's nothing important. I want you to call Jimmy instead——</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_Shakespeare">——Let's have him decide who looks the cutest in these new clothes.</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualNormalClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressScreamClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">...Hey!</speak>
            <show chara="AliceSmileCloseE" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Alice">...Hehe. Understood. Please wait a moment.</speak>
            <hide position="left"></hide>
            <hide position="right"></hide>
            <speak chara="_Alice">...Jimmy-san! The Captain is calling for you!</speak>
            <goto goto="170" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="170" background="deepWater.jpg">
            <bgm src="01_18_tango.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <text>On a certain day in the 13th century BC, at Mount Ida in the outskirts of Troy, Prince Paris was tasked with giving a golden apple to the 「most beautiful Goddess」. The candidates were the Queen of the Gods Hera, the Goddess of Wisdom and Warfare Athena, and the Goddess of Love Aphrodite.</text>
            <text>「O handsome Prince Jimmy Paris, please tell us, who is worthy of getting this large, gorgeous and invaluable golden apple?」</text>
            <text>「I am Hera Shakespeare. If you give me the golden apple, I promise I'll make you the richest man in the world.」</text>
            <text>「Paris-sama, I am Aphrodite Rossweisse. If you were to give me the golden apple, I will bestow my blessing upon you so that you may never experience unhappiness in your love life.」</text>
            <text>「Listen, you fool! The one who should have the golden apple is me, Athena Ataegina! Hand it over and I'll turn you into an invincible hero!」</text>
            <text>——A bunch of nonsense.</text>
            <text>After all in the outside world it's March 5th 2012—— Not even in a bubble world in the Quantum Sea the Goddesses will begin to fight out of love.</text>
            <text>...However, just as the sun rose in the horizon, the crew of the Caledonia were involved in another kind of battle.</text>
            <goto goto="180" clockwise="1"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="180" background="black">
            <bgm src="01_21_1-second-of-silence.mp3" status="stop"></bgm>
            <text remark="next">Next day, 12.19.19.17.18 2-Flint of the Mayan Calendar of Yucatan——</text>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX1+RLgYWFCb0+htv8E3C">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">严格来说，这个日期的前半部分（12.19.19.17.18）是属于长纪历的，而后半部分（2-燧石）则属于以260天为周期循环往复的“卓尔金历”（Tzolk'in，类似于干支系统）。</p>
                <p class="article-text">玛雅人的长纪历使用一连串向前进位的数字表示日期与年代，大致上以20为基数。日数的单位称为金（k'in），而20金为1乌纳（winal或uinal），18乌纳为1盾（tun，360天，约1年），20盾为1卡盾（k'atun，约19.7年），20卡盾为1伯克盾（bak'tun，约394.3年）。而比“伯克盾”更高、但极少被使用的四个单位，则依序为皮克盾（Pictun，约7885年）、卡拉盾（Calabtun，约157703年）、金奇盾（Kinchiltun，约3154069年）及阿托盾（Alautun，约63081377年）。</p>
                <p class="article-text">p.s. 在我们的世界里，2012年12月21日的长纪历对应数字是：13.0.0.0.0。（这让它有了所谓“世界末日”的意义。）</p>
            </remark>
            <goto goto="190" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="190" background="mayanVillage.jpg">
            <bgm src="legion.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">This is your last warning.</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">If you reject the teachings of God and decide to celebrate the 「New Era」 in such barbaric way——</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">We will break the ceasefire treaty of the sacred holiday and put a stop to your celebration with violence.</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="PriestAngryClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_PriestNoName">Hmph. Bunch of faithless dogs of the Federation!</speak>
            <show chara="PriestSeriousClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_PriestNoName">The 「ceasefire treaty of the sacred holiday」? Have you forgotten the traditions your ancestors left behind?</speak>
            <show chara="PriestSeriousClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="WarriorClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_WarriorNoName">Unforgivable! How you dare, you barbarians reject the teachings of the High Priestess——</speak>
            <show chara="WarriorClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">——Stop.</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">Our words can no longer reach them.</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">Let them be cursed forever by the Gods of Venus.</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="WitchSeriousClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_WitchNoName">Grandma, Federation Officer, please stop. Don't fight anymore!</speak>
            <show chara="WitchSeriousClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">...Hm?</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="PriestCalmClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_PriestNoName">Don't be silly, you think they would stop just because you asked them to?</speak>
            <show chara="PriestCalmClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <bgm src="bigTask.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="biankaDressDarkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_BiankaOutsiderNoName">Heh.</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressDarkClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_OfficerNoName">...Who are you?</speak>
            <show chara="OfficerClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="biankaDressSneerClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_BiankaOutsiderNoName">You wouldn't understand even if I told you but——</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShoutClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_BiankaOutsiderNoName">——I am a Valkyrie who uses violence to suppress violence!</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShoutClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_BiankaOutsiderNoName">Captain, say something too!</speak>
            <show chara="biankaDressShoutClose" position="right" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="shakesCasualConfidentClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_ShakespeareOutsiderNoName">Cough. As the saying goes, harmony brings wealth—— May I ask you to quell your anger?</speak>
            <show chara="shakesCasualLaughClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_ShakespeareOutsiderNoName">The Gods willed my ship to land at this exact moment——</speak>
            <speak chara="_ShakespeareOutsiderNoName">——Taking that into consideration, why don't you two make a truce?</speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX19HfLhF9LrPGSRzvmiU"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
