<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
    <story>
        <scene id="0" background="bg.jpg">
            <bgm src="11_12_mid-lude.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <cg src="11_12_newChapter.png" bg="bg.jpg"></cg>
            <goto goto="20" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="20" background="iranStory.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_01_ChichenItza.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="back"/>
            <show chara="zahhakYoung" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Once upon a time, Iran had a ruler known as the 「Serpent King」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">His name was Zahhak. He used to be a Prince from a remote frontier tribe before taking the throne.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Zahhak was a small and slender but healthy man. Contrary to what his appearance would suggest, he was a curious and kind man at heart.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">One day, Zahhak fell down a cliff during a hunt and met a witch who called herself 「Grey Serpent」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The witch kissed the Prince's shoulders and his broken legs were healed. Rather, it would be correct to say they were stronger than before.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakYoung" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The Prince was overjoyed and asked the witch what she would like in return.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">「Grey Serpent」 simply smiled and told the Prince: 「O future King of Kings, your thanks are more than enough. For you will leave the realm of man and bring joy to us all.」</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Back then, Zahhak was unaware of what kind of changes were occurring inside of him.</speak>
            <show chara="oldKingMoon" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The Prince's father, Merdas, would always go out for a stroll at night in the palace's gardens. The King was surrounded by flowers and admiring the Moon when the Prince arrived, excited to tell him about what had happened to him.</speak>
            <show chara="oldKingNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">「My dear son... what happened to you? You have such scary look on your face.」 The puzzled old man asked to his only son.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">But Zahhak did not answer. For some reason, the sight of his father wearing a crown and holding a scepter made him feel unusually hungry.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">His shoulders started to tingle so badly he began to scratch them with his hands. And then——</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——A serpent's head came out from each shoulder.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The Prince froze while the serpents, like an arrow, headed straight for the King's neck and bit him.</speak>
            <show chara="black" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The confused Zahhak composed himself, took out his sword and slashed the serpents——</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——But after cutting their heads, another one would grow from his shoulders.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Meanwhile, the King was poisoned by the serpents and had bubbles coming out of his mouth.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakSword" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Zahhak could no longer endure his hunger,</speak>
            <show chara="black" position="back"/>
            <show chara="bloodStain" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">and using his sword, he cut this father's head and fed his brain to the serpents.</speak>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="back"/>
            <show chara="zahhakSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">...That was the moment he became the horrifying 「Serpent King」.</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Afterwards, Zahhak ordered his subjects to bring him a criminal each night, and he fed their brains to the serpents.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Soon after there were no more criminals. To escape from his guilt, Zahhak waged war against the other tribes, defeated them and put them on trial——</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakAxe" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——And of course, he cut off the heads of those he found 「guilty」.</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The 「Serpent King」 was no longer that small and weak Prince who once died during a hunt.</speak>
            <!-- TYPO: tore -> tear -->
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">He could tore apart his enemies with his bare hands, and his skin was so hard it could not be harmed by any weapon.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The 「Serpent King」's army continued to win battle after battle.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakShah" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">He not only unified the tribes but took down the dynasty, and became known as the 「King of Kings」, the world's supreme ruler.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakAxe" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Then the 「King of Kings」 put in place strict laws in his country——</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——Every day someone will be sentenced to death. All so he could feed their brain without remorse.</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">And so hundreds of years passed by.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The 「Serpent King」 became old, his ways of governing no longer fitted the current era, and he became increasingly more violent——</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——That was when finally a hero finally appeared.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The hero led a subjugation force against Zahhak. However, Zahhak was immortal.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even after the hero cut off his head, the serpents continued to live and control his body.</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakNoHead" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_zahhak">「You damn fools... I've united our nation, destroyed our enemies, killed all the criminals and sentenced corrupt officers to death...」</speak>
            <speak chara="_zahhak">「And this is how you repay your debt to me?」</speak>
            <speak chara="_zahhak">「I suppose your ancestors never told you why I'm called the 「Serpent King」!」</speak>
            <show chara="zahhakNoHead" position="center" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="graySnakeNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">...In that moment, that witch 「Grey Serpent」 showed herself.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">「Ahh, poor King Zahhak. You made a grave mistake in the most crucial part. That is why you arrived at this pitiful ending.」 The witch said with a sad tone.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSmile" position="center" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="graySnakeNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Humanity exists to be surpassed.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">It's the kind of existence that would make one be ashamed of what they used to be once one transcends their own humanity.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">I gave you a chance to stop being an animal and become human, but you chose to remain an animal.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Revolutionaries, I speak of the future. The soul does not respect the human flesh.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Our instincts are like the impure flow of river——</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">——Only a sea, an existence that transcends rivers and lakes, can accept all impurities without losing itself.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">O sad King Zahhak, you destroyed your own soul in your attempt to surpass 「humanity」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">I thought if your soul were to look down upon your body you would be able to leave the shackles of instincts behind.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">But in truth your soul was as disgraceful as your body.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSilence" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">O pitiful King Zahhak, your soul refused to understand your flesh, so the flesh was dragged away by desire into an abyss.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">The serpents on your shoulders never desired human brains. All they wished was to help you in becoming a king as soon as possible.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSpeak" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Have you not noticed? The wisdom of the brains you ate became a part of you.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">That is why you became such a strong ruler and an excellent criminal.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">I called you 「the future King of Kings」 but alas, it seems you did not understand anything at all.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Those serpents were only fulfilling your basic desires of the flesh.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">O foolish King Zahhak, life is deal you can't take back, and you didn't even know what you were trading.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">I gave you the potential to surpass humanity, and you wasted it 「playing house」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Zahhak, you have no longer the potential to 「surpass humanity」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">Let us end this deal here.</speak>
            <show chara="graySnakeSmile" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_graySnake">...You were a rare specimen, but you are not the 「Super Human」 my Lord wanted.</speak>
            <hide position="center"></hide>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Saying that, the witch threw a dart and stabbed Zahhak's chest.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The former 「King of Kings」 made a loud sound as his body hit the ground, and the serpents on his shoulders withered and died. The witch then began to speak of the 「sacrifice」 that took place before their eyes to the confused crowd.</speak>
            <goto goto="30" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="30" background="asteroidPalace.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_01_Tuluum.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="ZarathustraThinkClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——That is the story of the 「Serpent King」 my father taught me.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Until the age of 15 I thought it was simply a baseless legend.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">But...</speak>
            <goto goto="40" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="40" background="scythianStory.jpg">
            <bgm src="legion.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="memoryLoading" position="back"/>
            <show chara="oldZaraNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Esther, I know this is sudden, but this might be the last time I'll be able to talk to you.</speak>
            <show chara="oldZaraAngry" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_oldZara" remark="next">Our place in the war has changed drastically. The King's army, 「The Immortals」, fell pray to an ambush by the Sacae. The King is probably already...</speak>
            <remark post="U2FsdGVkX18ZP0Od3QyqZ58AYwfj">
                <p class="article-text-h">注：</p>
                <p class="article-text">长生军（Ἀθάνατοι）——这是古希腊历史学家希罗多德（Ἡρόδοτος，约前484年~前425年）对阿契美尼德王朝中央禁军的称呼。</p>
                <p class="article-text">希罗多德将“长生军”描述为一支由重装步兵组成的精锐部队，其人数恰好保持在一万人不变。他声称，在这支部队中，任何战死、重伤或重病的士兵，都会立即被一名新的士兵取代。</p>
                <p class="article-text">然而，波斯方面的记载虽然印证了这样一支精锐禁军的存在，却称其为“伙伴军团”，而不是“长生军”。希罗多德、或是他的某个消息来源，可能是将古波斯语中的"Anûšiya"（“伙伴”）与"Anauša"（“长生者”）弄混了，并添油加醋地自行解释了一番。</p>
            </remark>
            <show chara="oldZaraNormal" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">The army has no leader right now and Prince Cambyses is far away in Babylonia. As the High Priest, I must go to the front lines and take charge of the army in place of the missing King.</speak>
            <!-- FLOW: gonna -> going to (probably more appropriate for a person giving his final words to his adopted daughter) -->
            <speak chara="_oldZara">There is no guarantee I'll come back alive. That's why I'm gonna give you these two things. I'm sure they'll help you in times of need.</speak>
            <show chara="oldZaraInjector" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">The first one is this drug. If you need the strength to fight, remove the cover and pierce your skin with the needle.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">You will then gain the strength of the legendary 「Serpent King」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">...「Serpent King」?</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Yeah, the 「Serpent King」. That legend is not nonsense.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">The King and me once met that 「Grey Serpent」 witch. We got this drug from her.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">But...</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">I'm aware this power is dangerous. This is a way of becoming a 「Super Human」—— But it's the worst of them all.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Which is why I also want to give you this other thing.</speak>
            <show chara="oldZaraGenius" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">It's a transfer device left behind by the previous civilization. If you use it, you'll be able to go back to your former life.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">My former... life?</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">What do you mean?</speak>
            <bgm src="02_22_amazingGrace.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Listen, Esther... I'm not your real father.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Your mother didn't die during childbirth either. I met you for the first time in the den of that 「Grey Serpent」 witch.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">W-What?</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">It happened a long time ago, when the King was just a Prince and I was a nameless naturalist.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">In one of our travels, we found a clue that lead us to the legendary witch—— 「Grey Serpent」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">We who were fearless explorers, pretended to be believers and made contact with her. Then, we assassinated her.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">「Grey Serpent」 had many magic tools in her den—— Among them, there was the machine that gave birth to you.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">...Machine? I was artificially made?</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">That I don't know.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">That machine was special—— At the time we couldn't read any of the letters, but it was clear to us it was counting down to something——</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">I, who didn't have the responsibility of 「seeing the world as a Prince」 like the King had——</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Stayed behind in 「Grey Serpent」's den to study her magic.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">...20 years passed by.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">The magic tools left behind by the witch were certainly impressive but—— Aside from a few words I couldn't understand much of her strange language.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">When I was about to give up due to my lack of progress——</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">At the evening of an early Summer, the countdown of that machine finally reached zero.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">The cover of the machine opened up like a flower spreading its petals, and a pleasant cold breeze touched my feet.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">...That was the moment you were born, Esther.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Raising you gave a new purpose to my life. I was even able to take a peek at the mystery behind 「God」 and 「Magic」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">I suspect you were a kid who was taken away from the hands of time by that machine 「Grey Serpent」 had.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Just like the many witches and sages of the past—— You were capable of naturally reading their strange language.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">I wasn't able to understand that language due to reaching 「enlightenment」 and I didn't build our religion.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">They were all things I learned from you before you arrived.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Thanks to your birth, I learned of the timeless will of an ancient civilization.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Thanks to your birth, I learned the concept and value of 「Super Human」.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Thanks to your birth, I learned what the opposite Gods are competing for.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Esther, child of the stars...</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">You are the genuine 「Son of God」. Even if the Sacae slaughter us all, you must survive at all costs.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">But father...</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Let me say it again. No matter what happens to me, to someone else or even the country, you must survive at all costs.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">In case of emergency, use this transfer device called 「Gnius」. It will let you sail beyond time and space, beyond the 「Sea of Mystery」, and take you to the 「world of light」 gifted by the Gods.</speak>
            <speak chara="_oldZara">Because that is the place you originally were from.</speak>
            <goto goto="50" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="50" background="asteroidPalace.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_01_Tuluum.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="biankaDressShockClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Bianka">「Gnius」, you said? Could it be——</speak>
            <show chara="ritaVestHesitateClose" position="left"/>
            <speak chara="_Rita">——High Priestess Esther, by 「originally」 you mean you were a resident of this world?</speak>
            <show chara="ritaVestHesitateClose" position="left" opacity="0.8"/>
            <show chara="ZarathustraSorrowClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">...No. That was merely what my father believed.</speak>
            <show chara="ZarathustraNormalClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">When the Sacae made their way into the castle, I destroyed all of his research and activated the 「Gnius」.</speak>
            <show chara="ZarathustraThinkClose" position="right"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The world around me was distorted at an incredible speed, and I began to look for the 「world of light」 my father talked about——</speak>
            <goto goto="60" change="#000000"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="60" background="manderlbrot13.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">——But what awaited me was an endless abyss devoid of everything.</speak>
            <goto goto="70" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="70" background="manderlbrot12.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even with my eyes closed, I would still see a crack in space.</speak>
            <goto goto="80" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="80" background="manderlbrot11.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even with my ears blocked, I would still hear the soft whispers of the stars.</speak>
            <goto goto="90" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="90" background="manderlbrot10.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even with my lips sealed, I would still feel an iron-like bitterness taste in my mouth.</speak>
            <goto goto="100" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="100" background="manderlbrot09.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even with my breath held, I would still feel as if my throat was burned by a fiery fire and smoke.</speak>
            <goto goto="110" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="110" background="manderlbrot08.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Even after drawing a Mandala, I would still feel pain in my fingertips as if they were burning.</speak>
            <goto goto="120" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="120" background="manderlbrot07.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">A moment outside the abyss felt like thousands of years inside of it.</speak>
            <goto goto="130" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="130" background="manderlbrot06.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Space and time lost all meaning. Without a path nor a compass to follow, I was a cracked ego drifting in the void.</speak>
            <goto goto="140" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="140" background="manderlbrot05.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">My body, my soul. My nerves, my brain. My blood, my heart—— It felt like every piece of me was screaming in agony, unable to work properly.</speak>
            <goto goto="150" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="150" background="manderlbrot04.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">There was no 「world of light」 after all.</speak>
            <goto goto="160" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="160" background="manderlbrot03.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Eternity, infinity, something that keeps people alive forever... It was hell itself.</speak>
            <goto goto="170" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="170" background="manderlbrot02.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">When I got used to the suffering and my body, soul and mind became one again——</speak>
            <goto goto="180" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="180" background="manderlbrot01.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">I finally understood the truth behind this endless cycle, this endless abyss. It was not a truth one can see with their eyes, but with their heart.</speak>
            <goto goto="190" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="190" background="manderlbrot00.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_14_equipment.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">That was the heart of a devil, an equation buried by the Gods of Light.</speak>
            <goto goto="200" change="#ffffff"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="200" background="asteroidPalace.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_01_Tuluum.mp3" status="start"></bgm>
            <show chara="ZarathustraSmileClose" position="center"/>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">I shall end my tale here.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">The night is upon us, the breeze gets colder, and people enter their deepest dreams.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">No pain or sentiment.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">O soul, let us wash away your trivial disgrace and immorality. Only then everyone will be able to greet the light of day once again.</speak>
            <goto goto="210" change="0"/>
        </scene>
        <scene id="210" background="CG15-1.jpg">
            <bgm src="06_01_Tuluum.mp3" status="continue"></bgm>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">Let yourself be devoured by me. Become one with me in death and sleep forever inside my soul.</speak>
            <speak chara="_ZarathustraDaughter">There is only room for 「one」 Super Human in this husk that drifts beyond endlessness and nothingness.</speak>
            <end post="U2FsdGVkX18hKC2MgZAA1oJbC8G9"/>
        </scene>
    </story>
</data>
